<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[685]]></id><name><![CDATA[productmedia]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Media (Audio / Video)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Vídeos & Música]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Enrich your product descriptions with explanatory videos and video or audio previews!  The Product Media module lets you import your own media content (audio and video files) and easily add it to your]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/videos-musica/685-product-media-audio-video.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/685.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Enrich your product descriptions with explanatory videos and video or audio previews!  The Product Media module lets you import your own media content (audio and video files) and easily add it to your product pages.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Make your product pages more interactive and your products more accessibleGive more information on your products: benefits, a better description, recommendations for use, etc.Easily increase your conversion rateBoost your sales and reduce the return rate of your products]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611425-pprod/product-media-audio-video.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611425-pbig/product-media-audio-video.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Vendas cruzadas & Pacotes de produtos]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Permite a venda de pacotes com o uso de quaisquer estoques de produtos disponíveis que façam parte desses pacotes e oferece a oportunidade de aplicar operações de negócios]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/vendas-cruzadas-pacotes-produtos/1015-advanced-pack-5.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Permite a venda de pacotes com o uso de quaisquer estoques de produtos disponíveis que façam parte desses pacotes e oferece a oportunidade de aplicar operações de negócios. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Permita a compra de combinações de produtos com ou sem um desconto com apenas um clique  Você gostaria de aumentar a média do seu carrinho de compras e, ao mesmo tempo, permitir que seus clientes economizem dinheiro se comprarem vários produtos ao mesmo tempo? Agora isso é possível graças ao Advanced Pack!  Sem mais perda de tempo, você tem a possibilidade de criar pacotes de produtos que podem ser comprados com um clique, sem se preocupar com o estoque de suas combinações.  Uma preciosa ferramenta adicional de vendas  Acompanhe seus clientes em seus processos de compra ao oferecer-lhes pacotes de produtos relacionados que você tenha predefinido, da mesma forma que faria um vendedor em uma loja de verdade. Por exemplo: esta câmera fantástica, cartão de memória ou tripé. Você sabe que esta escolha é apropriada e que será atraente para seus clientes.  Ou você pode até mesmo usar seus produtos mais vendidos, adicionando-os àqueles que tenham menor visibilidade, permitindo dessa forma que seus clientes os descubram.  Seus pacotes deverão ser feitos com um mínimo de dois produtos, a quantidade total é ilimitada. Defina a quantidade por produto e escolha as combinações de sua preferência. Há várias opções que permitem múltiplas possibilidades.  Você gostaria de reservar a compra de um produto dentro de um pacote? Isso também é possível. Dessa forma, você poderá oferecer um produto gratuito se ele for comprado como parte de um pacote. As possibilidades são infinitas!  Assistente integrado  Nem sempre é fácil decidir quais produtos devem ser oferecidos dentro de um pacote. Mais uma vez, o Advanced Pack tem a solução para seu problema. Ao criar seu pacote, nosso módulo lhe fornecerá informações estratégicas, como a quantidade de produtos vendidos ou seus estoques disponíveis. Também há um simulador dinâmico de preços para o seu pacote, que lhe ajudará a ver de forma mais clara quando estiver criando sua transação de negócios, sem causar prejuízos à sua margem de lucro.  Esteja no comando das combinações  Um dos produtos que você adicionou em seu pacote está disponível em várias cores, mas você não quer oferecer todos eles nesse conjunto? O Advanced Pack lhe permitirá fazer isso.  Você terá a possibilidade de predefinir uma combinação por padrão para cada produto do seu pacote, mesmo que ele seja diferente daquele definido em seu catálogo.  Seus clientes poderão então personalizar suas escolhas entre as características que você tiver escolhido para integrar a oferta.  Incentivo de negócios  O incentivo é algo que motiva seus visitantes a fazerem uma compra. O objetivo principal é convencer um maior número de visitantes do seu site a concluir seus pedidos e/ou gastar mais por transação. Talvez você já tenha tentado com ofertas de frete grátis para uma certa quantidade de compras, oferecendo descontos em certos produtos ou até mesmo enviando vouchers de desconto? Todos esses métodos funcionam, mas seus alcances são limitados, já que essas promoções costumam ser temporárias devido a seus custos excessivos! Pare de procurar – você já encontrou a solução!  Para atrair seus clientes, o Advanced Pack dará a você a opção de aplicar um desconto quando o pedido de todos os produtos do carrinho de compras for feito, o que incentivará a compra do pacote completo.  Três possibilidades estão disponíveis: Oferecer um desconto específico sobre cada produto no pacote.Aplicar um desconto geral sobre o conjunto de produtos.Aplicar um preço fixo, como um preço psicológico, por exemplo.O Advanced Pack também poderá gerenciar os descontos já aplicados aos seus produtos, permitindo a você integrá-los ao preço do pacote ou, ao contrário, excluí-los para escolher o desconto predefinido sobre o pacote. Essa decisão será ainda mais fácil graças à nossa interface de aparência simples e clara, que lhe permitirá ver os produtos com desconto com grande facilidade.  Você não precisará mais se preocupar com a consistência dos seus preços  Você já teve de revisar todos os preços no seu catálogo para identificar possíveis inconsistências e corrigi-las? O que aconteceria se você tivesse de gerenciar manualmente as repercussões dessas mudanças na precificação de produtos em seus pacotes? Isso representaria uma carga de trabalho extra significativa se não for antecipada entre a escolha de soluções de gerenciamento dentro dos pacotes.  Mais uma vez, o Advanced Pack tem a solução.  Por padrão, caso nenhuma redução tenha sido aplicada, o preço do pacote será a soma dos produtos nele contidos. Se você precisar alterar o preço de um produto depois de ter criado o pacote, o preço do pacote será atualizado automaticamente, e sem que você tenha de interferir.  Nesses casos em que você aplique um desconto a um ou mais produtos em um pacote existente, e sobre condições em que você tenha autorizado implicações promocionais, o preço do pacote também será alterado, apresentando a seus clientes o desconto aplicado.  Um dos produtos do seu pacote está sujeito a um imposto ambiental? Sem problema! Ele será repassado automaticamente ao preço do pacote e será indicado claramente, garantindo absoluto respeito à legislação.  Considerando o gerenciamento do seu estoque, tudo foi automatizado!  Para cada pacote encomendado, os estoques dos produtos que o compõem serão descontados automaticamente. Dessa forma, você evitará um duplo gerenciamento de estoque ou a frustração gerada por vendas inviabilizadas devido à má atribuição de quantidades. Além disso, no caso de um produto de um pacote estar esgotado, ele será automaticamente apresentado como indisponível para compra graças a um sistema de aviso de indisponibilidade elegante e moderno.  Para os clientes, integramos um sistema de notificação gráfico e divertido, que permite a identificação instantânea de faltas de estoque em combinações ou produtos que integram o pacote. Não há a possibilidade de você receber encomendas de produtos que estejam esgotados!  Dê destaque a seus pacotes e venda mais  Assim que definir seu pacote, você poderá configurá-lo da mesma forma que configura um produto normal. Tudo é possível, como atribuir-lhe imagens personalizadas, classificá-lo na categoria de sua escolha, otimizar sua ocorrência em motores de busca, inserir uma descrição personalizada, atribuir-lhe um código EAN ou uma referência específica, configurar seu volume para cálculo de custos de entrega, entre outras opções.  Pensando naqueles que têm pouco tempo, e para facilitar seu marketing, o Advanced Pack apresentará automaticamente todas as fotos e descrições dos produtos que o compõem no formato de abas. Seus clientes serão informados corretamente, sem precisarem deixar a página de seu pacote, e podem concluir suas compras com apenas um clique.  E isso não é tudo… Para ganharem mais visibilidade, seus pacotes serão automaticamente destacados em suas fichas informativas para aqueles que estão sendo vendidos em quantidade. Dessa forma, você incentivará seus clientes a fazer o pedido do pacote, e não só do produto em que estavam inicialmente interessados. Essencialmente, isso é venda-cruzada: um método acessível para aumentar a média do seu carrinho de compras!  Não nos esquecemos dos designers  Desde o início, integramos o conceito de que nosso módulo deve ser facilmente adaptado por sua agência web ou designer/integrador. O módulo adapta-se perfeitamente aos temas padrão do PrestaShop 1.5 e 1.6, permitindo ao mesmo tempo o máximo de personalização gráfica avançada.  Um conjunto de modelos JavaScript e folhas em estilo CSS são entregues em modelos com o módulo para facilitar o processo de integração. Dessa forma, você mesmo ou o integrador poderão utilizar todas as funcionalidades do motor do Advanced Pack 5 para apresentá-los no formato gráfico que corresponda da melhor forma ao clima geral da sua loja on-line.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[299.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[219.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1048]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsshoptab]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shop Pro for THE Social Network]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Produtos nas Facebook & Redes Sociais]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Set up a "Shop" tab on your Facebook page and increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website. Boost your Facebook community]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/produtos-nas-facebook-redes-sociais/1048-shop-pro-for-the-social-network.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1048.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Set up a "Shop" tab on your Facebook page and increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website. Boost your Facebook community.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2011 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  Show your products directly on the social network. Effective way to boost your sales, enjoy the power of your Facebook community to communicate about your shop and increase the number of visitors and orders on your PrestaShop store.  LEVERAGE THE POWER OF YOUR FACEBOOK CUMMUNITY TO GENERATE TRAFFIC AND SALES ON YOUR SHOP Increase the number of visitors and potential buyers on your PrestaShop website and boost your Facebook community. It’s a real way to grow your sales: take advantage of your Facebook community to communicate and bring your audience to your shop. This module is compatible with the multishop feature.Shop Pro for THE Social Network is also compatible with most shared SSL certificates (certified to work with OVH shared SSL hosting) The module also lets integrate statistics tracking via Google Analytics to measure its performance A live built-in preview of the module will help you set it up, and you can then easily link it to your Facebook page in a single click. "Shop Pro for THE Social Network" will help you improve your brand image and reach.  INCREASE THE NUMBER OF « LIKES » ON YOUR PRODUCTS AND THEIR VISIBILITY For each product, a "Like" button is included, which will allow visitors to share and talk about your products. Clicks on"Like" buttons will have impact on your website’s SEO and its position in Google search results. We also offer you to go even further : use your Google Analytics code to get your statistics as to the effectiveness of your Facebook Shop.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/835133-pprod/shop-pro-for-the-social-network.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/835133-pbig/shop-pro-for-the-social-network.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Rastreamento da entrega]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Voc&ecirc; usa o servi&ccedil;o de entrega da UPS, transportadora imprescind&iacute;vel renomada por sua rapidez e seguran&ccedil;a?  Facilite sua vida e melhore a satisfa&ccedil;&atilde;o do cliente ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/rastreamento-entrega/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Voc&ecirc; usa o servi&ccedil;o de entrega da UPS, transportadora imprescind&iacute;vel renomada por sua rapidez e seguran&ccedil;a?  Facilite sua vida e melhore a satisfa&ccedil;&atilde;o do cliente gra&ccedil;as ao m&oacute;dulo UPS Monitoramento de Entrega que facilitar&aacute; o monitoramento dos seus envios no mundo inteiro.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Desfrute dos benef&iacute;cios dos servi&ccedil;os da UPS e do m&oacute;dulo de monitoramento de entrega UPS:Entregue todos os seus pedidos no seu pa&iacute;s ou no exterior gra&ccedil;as ao desempenho da rede de distribui&ccedil;&atilde;o da UPS;Usufrua do monitoramento avan&ccedil;ado dos seus envios, etapa por etapa, diretamente do seu back-office;Reduza os prazos de entrega e melhore a experi&ecirc;ncia global de compra dos seus clientes gra&ccedil;as a uma qualidade otimizada de entrega.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1768]]></id><name><![CDATA[gmerchantcenter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Comparadores de preços]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/comparadores-precos/1768-google-merchant-center-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.&nbsp;The performance of Google Adwords Shopping campaigns and your presence in the &quot;Shopping&quot; results of Google&#39;s search engine largely depends on the quality of your Google Merchant Center feed and completeness of your data. The more information accurate you include, the better the results ! This very complete module will let you achieve just that and maximize your chances of obtaining good rankings on Google Shopping, while minimizing the time you will need to spend to have all your products accepted by Google.&nbsp;Instantly boost your traffic : Google Shopping and Adwords benefit from hundreds of millions of hits each month. Moreover this traffic is highly targeted and brings qualified visitors to your shop&nbsp;Increase your sales and ROI : Because traffic is extremely targeted, Google Shopping and Google Adwords Shopping Campaigns provide you with one of the highest return on investment rates compared to other marketing channels and is very cost effective&nbsp;Present in over 37 countries as of today, Google Shopping is a fast track start for international expansion&nbsp;&nbsp;With nearly 6000 copies sold, 460+ reviews and an average 5/5 rating, our Google Merchant Center module is hands down the most robust, accurate, powerful and complete module for Google Shopping.&nbsp;We also have extensive knowledge and experience on the ins and outs of Google&#39;s rather complex requirements, and our tech support team will gladly help answer your questions to the best of their ability !&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For power users and SEM agencies, for even more great features, including advanced custom labels management, promotions feed and quick inventory feed, you may be interested in purchasing the PRO version of the module available on&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/price-comparison/20908-google-merchant-center-pro-google-shopping.html&nbsp;&nbsp;This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the&nbsp;2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for &quot;Best module&quot;, with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module.&nbsp;Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support&nbsp;: when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.7.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[144.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/749677-pprod/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/749677-pbig/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2072]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedtopmenu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu - Responsive]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Menu]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Localize e selecione o m&oacute;dulo de menu responsive a mais popular e mais avan&ccedil;ada dispon&iacute;vel para PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/menu/2072-advanced-top-menu-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2072.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Localize e selecione o m&oacute;dulo de menu responsive a mais popular e mais avan&ccedil;ada dispon&iacute;vel para PrestaShop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Construa qualquer tipo de barra de navega&ccedil;&atilde;o horizontal!&nbsp;Menu Avan&ccedil;ado&nbsp;isso ir&aacute; ajud&aacute;-lo a simplificar a navega&ccedil;&atilde;o e a utiliza&ccedil;&atilde;o do seu site, apresentando aos seus visitantes uma&nbsp;vis&atilde;o global do seu cat&aacute;logo&nbsp;a fim de gui&aacute;-los a encontrar rapidamente o produto desejado.&nbsp;&nbsp;Devido &agrave; sua constru&ccedil;&atilde;o&nbsp;altamente modular&nbsp;, voc&ecirc; poder&aacute; usar a sua barra de menu para apresentar imagens, promo&ccedil;&otilde;es ou an&uacute;ncios, com o intuito de&nbsp;destacar as suas ofertas ou servi&ccedil;os&nbsp;que tornam a sua loja uma refer&ecirc;ncia comercial.&nbsp;Com uma interface de vasta configura&ccedil;&atilde;o, o que lhe permitir&aacute; personalizar a sua barra de menu&nbsp;sem que haja necessidade de um conhecimento t&eacute;cnico especial:ResponsiveN&uacute;mero ilimitado de abasQuantidade ilimitada de colunasIlimitado n&uacute;mero de elementosPersonaliza&ccedil;&atilde;o gr&aacute;fica simples e completaCria&ccedil;&atilde;o autom&aacute;tica do menu do seu cat&aacute;logoTodos os tipos de conte&uacute;do suportados: categorias, fabricantes, fornecedores, CMS, liga&ccedil;&atilde;o gratuita...Visualiza&ccedil;&atilde;o condicionada, dependendo do status do visitante&nbsp;A faster and cleaner configuration&nbsp;interfaceNew default&nbsp;theme for optimal&nbsp;design out of the boxNew appearance settingsNew specific settings for mobileA&nbsp;Sticky mode, which let your menu always visible regardless of scroller&nbsp;positionAllows you to restrict the display of some elements for desktop or mobile viewAllows you to add different images for each languageOpening animation effect on submenusDelay on opening submenusContextual help tips in Back Office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.12.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573526-pprod/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573526-pbig/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2376]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestagiftvouchers]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Coupons / Discount vouchers]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fidelização & Apadrinhamento]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Fidelize os clientes cadastrados oferecendo cupons de desconto para os pr&oacute;ximos pedidos!   Esse m&oacute;dulo, completo e de f&aacute;cil configura&ccedil;&atilde;o, permite gerar cupons de des]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/fidelizacao-apadrinhamento/2376-coupons-discount-vouchers.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2376.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Fidelize os clientes cadastrados oferecendo cupons de desconto para os pr&oacute;ximos pedidos!   Esse m&oacute;dulo, completo e de f&aacute;cil configura&ccedil;&atilde;o, permite gerar cupons de desconto e envi&aacute;-los automaticamente aos seus clientes logados e tendo feito algum tipo de pedido: compra de valor m&iacute;nimo, de produto espec&iacute;fico de uma dada categoria, etc. Voc&ecirc; decide conforme suas necessidades!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo Cupons de Desconto e Fidelidade voc&ecirc; pode:  &nbsp;Criar automaticamente regras de carrinho de compras para gerar c&oacute;digos de oferta enviados por e-mail aos seus clientes,&nbsp;Personalize o nome dos cupons, seu valor como uma porcentagem ou pre&ccedil;o e seu per&iacute;odo de validade,&nbsp;Aumente o tamanho m&eacute;dio do carrinho em seu site, definindo os valores m&iacute;nimos de compra para usar o cupom de desconto,&nbsp;Construir a fidelidade dos clientes, incentivando-os a comprar novamente em sua loja,&nbsp;Liquide facilmente o seu invent&aacute;rio de produtos de sua escolha e promova melhor seus novos produtos e categorias]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/708607-pprod/coupons-discount-vouchers.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/708607-pbig/coupons-discount-vouchers.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Revenda (marketplace)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/revenda-/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Exclusive PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world&rsquo;s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons&nbsp; since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.2.204]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[239.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pesquisa & Filtros]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[O melhor m&oacute;dulo de navega&ccedil;&atilde;o por facetas para PrestaShop ! Vencedor do Best Modules Awards]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pesquisa-filtros/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[O melhor m&oacute;dulo de navega&ccedil;&atilde;o por facetas para PrestaShop ! Vencedor do Best Modules Awards]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Ferramenta indispens&aacute;vel para as lojas que oferecem uma vasta sele&ccedil;&atilde;o de produtos, Advanced Search 4 permite adicionar os motores de busca que pretender e coloc&aacute;-los nos locais &agrave; sua escolha. &nbsp; A mec&acirc;nica de pesquisa do m&oacute;dulo baseia-se em filtros. Constituem a base de uma navega&ccedil;&atilde;o em facetas bem conseguida. Permitem aos seus clientes encontrar os produtos que correspondem aos seus crit&eacute;rios de pesquisa com um m&iacute;nimo de cliques. Advanced Search 4 foi desenvolvido com o intuito de proporcionar tempos de carregamento curtos, mesmo para os cat&aacute;logos com v&aacute;rias dezenas de milhares de produtos ou categorias. &nbsp; Primeira vers&atilde;o publicada em 2010 - Vencedor do Best Modules Awards em 2012 - Classificado entre os melhores Add-ons de vendas desde 2010. &nbsp; 3 tipos de pesquisas &agrave; sua disposi&ccedil;&atilde;o:Pesquisa em todo o cat&aacute;logo: o per&iacute;metro de pesquisa aplica-se a todo o cat&aacute;logo.Pesquisa numa sele&ccedil;&atilde;o de produtos: o per&iacute;metro de pesquisa aplica-se &agrave; p&aacute;gina na qual o cliente se encontra.Pesquisa por etapas: os crit&eacute;rios v&atilde;o-se refinando &agrave; medida que os seus clientes especificam a sua pesquisa.&nbsp; Para al&eacute;m da sua fun&ccedil;&atilde;o principal, o m&oacute;dulo Advanced Search &eacute; tamb&eacute;m reconhecido como um dos seus melhores aliados para referencia&ccedil;&atilde;o. Integra um gerador de p&aacute;ginas otimizadas para o SEO, o que lhe permite aumentar a sua visibilidade sem duplica&ccedil;&atilde;o do conte&uacute;do! &nbsp; Por detr&aacute;s de todas estas inova&ccedil;&otilde;es, o nosso objetivo continua a ser sempre o mesmo&nbsp;: Ajud&aacute;-lo a aumentar a sua taxa de convers&atilde;o e multiplicar as suas vendas ! Ir&aacute; compreender, com esta nova vers&atilde;o 4.11, Advanced Search nunca foi t&atilde;o performante]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.12.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[239.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/766622-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766622-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Edição rápida & em massa]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/edicao-rapida/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add to this category and add them in one click! You also can control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/741974-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2889]]></id><name><![CDATA[blockyoutubevideos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Videos - YouTube]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Vídeos & Música]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[D&ecirc; vida &agrave;s suas p&aacute;ginas de produto&nbsp;em seu site e torne-as interativas adicionando v&iacute;deos!  O m&oacute;dulo&nbsp;V&iacute;deos de Produto - YouTube&nbsp;&eacute; a manei]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/videos-musica/2889-product-videos-youtube.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2889.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[D&ecirc; vida &agrave;s suas p&aacute;ginas de produto&nbsp;em seu site e torne-as interativas adicionando v&iacute;deos!  O m&oacute;dulo&nbsp;V&iacute;deos de Produto - YouTube&nbsp;&eacute; a maneira ideal de aumentar a taxa de convers&atilde;o dos seus produtos. Ele permite que voc&ecirc; importe seus v&iacute;deos do YouTube de forma f&aacute;cil e autom&aacute;tica e adicione-os onde voc&ecirc; quiser em sua p&aacute;gina de produtos.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Os v&iacute;deos s&atilde;o uma ferramenta essencial para tornar os seus produtos mais atraentes e melhorar a sua taxa de convers&atilde;o.&nbsp;73% dos consumidores tendem a comprar um produto ou servi&ccedil;o ap&oacute;s assistirem a um v&iacute;deo.   Este m&oacute;dulo &eacute; uma ferramenta essencial para o seu site e seus clientes: &nbsp;Torne seus produtos mais atraentes oferecendo aos seus clientes informa&ccedil;&otilde;es visuais e relevantes complementares (recursos, caracter&iacute;sticas, benef&iacute;cios, uso etc.).&nbsp;Aumente sua taxa de convers&atilde;o&nbsp;e reduza a devolu&ccedil;&atilde;o de produtos. 96% dos consumidores pensa que &eacute; mais f&aacute;cil .chegar a uma decis&atilde;o sobre uma compra online ap&oacute;s assistirem a um v&iacute;deo.&nbsp;Enrique&ccedil;a facilmente o conte&uacute;do do seu site e melhore o seu SEO adicionando v&iacute;deos do YouTube &agrave;s suas p&aacute;ginas de produto.&nbsp;Melhore o engajamento do cliente&nbsp;e aumente o tamanho m&eacute;dio do carrinho em seu site.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/625269-pprod/product-videos-youtube.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625269-pbig/product-videos-youtube.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanagerforprestashop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Store Manager for PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Módulos PrestaShop]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently! *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE *** ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/modules-prestashop/2937-store-manager-for-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL! Back office solution you need, to manage your PrestaShop online store efficiently! *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE *** ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you.Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management.Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! Spend an Hour, Save a Day!Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds.For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you. Take Your Online Business to the BankBuy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules.Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn’t require any special skills, so you don’t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/572842-pprod/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/572842-pbig/store-manager-for-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Impressão de etiquetas Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Preparação & Remessa]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Poupe um tempo precioso automatizando a edi&ccedil;&atilde;o de suas etiquetas de envio! Este m&oacute;dulo para PrestaShop permite editar e imprimir etiquetas de envio para colar nos pacotes, com bas]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/preparacao-remessa/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Poupe um tempo precioso automatizando a edi&ccedil;&atilde;o de suas etiquetas de envio! Este m&oacute;dulo para PrestaShop permite editar e imprimir etiquetas de envio para colar nos pacotes, com base nos pedidos feitos no site. Voc&ecirc; pode optar por imprimir uma ou tr&ecirc;s etiquetas por p&aacute;gina, para melhor atender &agrave;s suas necessidades!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time shipping your ordersLower your rate of returned packages due to wrong addresses]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation...]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fidelização & Apadrinhamento]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/fidelizacao-apadrinhamento/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !&nbsp;This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[239.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4731]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestablog]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Professional blog]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blog, Fórum & Notícias]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best trafic module on prestashop award 2015]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/blog-forum-noticias/4731-professional-blog.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4731.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best trafic module on prestashop award 2015. The most complete blog published for PrestaShop, Fully compatible with every language and will fit perfectly in your system, whether or not multilingual and/or multishop!&nbsp;Optimized for a better SEO.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get in touch with your customers through a blog has become increasingly common for companies who want to build customer loyalty.No need to install a second cms to get all the features you need, this blog developed by the web agency HDClic is everything you need!&nbsp;Search Engine optimisation (SEO)&nbsp;SEO have been one of the most important part of our developpment of this module,&nbsp;It will be a perfect and infallible tool to increase your visibility on the web.&nbsp;Responsive Design&nbsp;Our webdesign team have developped a template who pefectly integrate in all type of template. Responsive or not.&nbsp;Fast support&nbsp;100% of our customers get an anwser within 1 hour to 12 hours maximum (period days worked) to help you as quickly as possible to implement your project.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/730685-pprod/professional-blog.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/730685-pbig/professional-blog.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (Referenciamento natural)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[ Melhore o seu SEO graças ao Link Building interno]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/seo-referenciamento-natural/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[ Melhore o seu SEO graças ao Link Building interno]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Otimize o SEO da sua loja PrestaShop  O Link Building interno consiste em criar links entre as páginas da sua loja, utilizando palavras-chaves sobre as quais quer obter um melhor posicionamento no Google.  Para otimizar da melhor forma o posicionamento do seu site Internet, é primordial implementar um Link Building que irá permitir que os motores de busca percorram a sua loja da maneira mais fácil possível. O objetivo é fornecer-lhes um máximo de informações com o menor número de cliques possíveis.  SEO Internal Linking otimiza para você a organização da navegação dentro da sua loja, e tem um papel essencial na sua estratégia de SEO.  Defina as expressões sobre as quais deseja ser referenciado assim como as páginas de destino, e deixe o módulo criar os links para você!  Se desejar adicionar links automáticos nas suas descrições de páginas categorias, pense em instalar o nosso módulo HTML on Descriptions.  Ter um bom Link Building interno é mesmo eficaz?  O Link Building interno com palavras-chaves específicos constitui um método de otimização que teve êxito. Sobretudo para melhorar a relevância de um conteúdo.  Entre as desvantagens, é preciso saber que a instalação desses links é longa e tediosa, necessita seguir regras de boa conduta SEO, para não fazer um excesso de otimização que poderia ser detectado pelo Google, e deve ser atualizado regularmente para seguir as mudanças do seu catálogo.  E nesse contexto que desenvolvemos este módulo, que lhe permitirá implementar centenas de links cruzados entre as suas páginas em alguns minutos, tendo a certeza que respeita os melhores guias de boas práticas SEO White Hat.  Foi pensado para acompanhar tanto as agências SEO quanto os comerciantes na Internet.  A sua utilização é das mais simples.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[179.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Análises & Estatísticas]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/analises-estatisticas/5255-advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get perfect visibility on your shop's and products' profitability !  The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly, profit and profit margin.  Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like "what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?".  This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011 PrestaShop Awards for Best module.    You are guaranteed to buy a quality module and to get fast and efficient tech support in case you need it.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.10.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[179.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/767436-pprod/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/767436-pbig/advanced-sales-tax-profit-and-profit-margin-reports.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5711]]></id><name><![CDATA[zipcodezone]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipping fees based on zipcodes]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Custo de frete]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/custo-de-frete/5711-shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5711.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With PrestaShop, it is possible to apply different shipping fees based on country or state. However, this does not necessarily represent the reality of carriers. Some will charge higher prices for mountainous or remote areas for example (departments or overseas territories). Improve your shop's shipping system with this module which will allow you to apply different shipping fees based on zip code of your client. Using the zone system of PrestaShop, you will be able to cut a country into as many parts as you want. By department, area or whatever you want. This has the advantage of adapting the way you want your areas. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/650424-pprod/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650424-pbig/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Revenda (marketplace)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/revenda-/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders. Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le March&eacute; is one of France&rsquo;s leading marketplaces.  Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success: - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount) - multiple delivery methods, etc.  Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.  1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices. In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products: - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace, - Prices and inventories are automatically updated, - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.  Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.  A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module&rsquo;s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants&nbsp;for the benefit of fellow e-merchants&nbsp;and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.  Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.   *This offer applies for merchants already registered on&nbsp;CleMarch&eacute;&nbsp;Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with&nbsp;any other ongoing&nbsp;Cdiscount.com&nbsp;offer.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.96]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[159.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/822598-pprod/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/822598-pbig/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6144]]></id><name><![CDATA[gsnippetsreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (Referenciamento natural)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful customer rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/seo-referenciamento-natural/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6144.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The most complete and powerful customer rating & review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With Google Rich Snippets, benefit from visually enhanced results on Google's search engine results and increase your click rate, numbers visitors and sales ! The full rating and review system will also greatly&nbsp;improve your shop's conversion rate and further increase your sales. If you have already purchased our Wall Posts for THE Social Network module (sold separately on https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/4429-wall-posts-for-the-social-network.html), you can have any rating / review automatically posted on your Facebook page. This module is also fully compatible and integrates with Presta-Module's "Advanced Pack 5" module, available on&nbsp;http://addons.prestashop.com/en/merchandising-prestashop-modules/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[119.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/761381-pprod/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/761381-pbig/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Administração dos Clientes]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/administracao-clientes/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/101289-pprod/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/101289-pbig/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6337]]></id><name><![CDATA[codfee]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cash On Delivery With Fee/Surcharge Plus (COD)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pagamento em dinheiro na entrega]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pagamento-dinheiro-entrega/6337-cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6337.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method. More than 5,000 downloads and highly rated!The favourite payment method for your customers!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ESSENTIAL MODULE! This module will increase your sales! You can offset the extra cost of this shipping method by charging a fee to the customer. The cash on delivery payment method allows your customers to pay for the order at the time of receiving their order, they pay on shipment. This payment method is the perfect solution for customers who do not trust other payment methods, such as a card payment or PayPal, and prefer to pay upon receiving their order. With this method, you can offset the additional cost normally associated with "cash on delivery" by charging a fee to customers that choose this payment method. This module allows you to add the "cash on delivery" payment method with the option of applying an extra fee. Compatible with back office orders! Also, you can configure as a pay upon cash on pickup! Customers will benefit from the payment options most used and preferred by them. This module DOES NOT require a monthly fee or any other fee, you buy it once and you use it without any restrictions. Our guarantees ✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote. Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812425-pprod/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812425-pbig/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6344]]></id><name><![CDATA[swissrounded]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Rounded to 5ct for Switzerland]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gestão de preços]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module enables the management of rounded to 5 cents on your shop. This module is recommended for e-Swiss merchants using PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/gestao-precos/6344-rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6344.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module enables the management of rounded to 5 cents on your shop. This module is recommended for e-Swiss merchants using PrestaShop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Show prices that are always rounded up to five cents, to avoid confusion when your customers navigate your store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[17.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/882910-pprod/rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/882910-pbig/rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Características sem limite !]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pesquisa & Filtros]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Ajuste as características do seu produto]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pesquisa-filtros/6356-multiple-features-caracteristicas-sem-limite-.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Ajuste as características do seu produto]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Acrescente características sem limite !  Com Multiple Features, existe a possibilidade de inscrever tantos valores quantos os necessários, para um mesmo produto, com as mesmas características. Pode, assim, fazer desaparecer uma limitação do PrestaShop servindo-se plenamente das suas características !  Se por acaso utiliza Advanced Search 4 (Vencedor do Prémio PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), oferece aos visitantes uma procura ainda mais adequada no seu catálogo.  Caso de cliente :  Ocarat.com: "Certas joias podem ter uma composição diferente e uma mistura de vários metais. O Back Office de PrestaShop oferece a possibilidade de associar uma caraterística a um produto. Ouro, eu pretendo integrar na minha loja uma aliança em outro decorada de diamantes e esmeraldas. Atualmente, a ficha características não me permite fazê-lo. Não posso inscrever vários valores num mesmo artigo. Tenho, portanto,de escolher entre ouro, diamantes e esmeraldas. Multiple Features tirou esta limitação !"]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-caracteristicas-sem-limite-.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-caracteristicas-sem-limite-.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6946]]></id><name><![CDATA[invoicepayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[O pagamento da fatura]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pagamento por fatura]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[pagamento por fatura é popular em muitos países]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pagamento-fatura/6946-o-pagamento-da-fatura.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6946.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[pagamento por fatura é popular em muitos países. Com este módulo, você pode oferecer o método de pagamento da fatura aos seus clientes registados a fim de proporcionar uma experiência de compra segura.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ Com este módulo, você pode oferecer um pagamento de contas para seus usuários. Você pode definir a partir de que ordersThis método de pagamento está disponível para os seus clientes. Por exemplo, para os seus clientes regulares este método shoulderstand estar disponível a partir de sua 2ª ordem. Você pode, portanto, definir o valor do pedido limite este método está disponível para. Além disso, você pode definir as condições de pagamento, que dependem do status do pedido selecionado. Após o status mudou, o prazo de pagamento Aparece, portanto, na factura PDF. Na configuração do módulo para que você tenha uma textarea para mais informações. Por exemplo, você pode especificar onde o cliente shoulderstand transferir o dinheiro para. Esta informação aparece na factura PDF]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689390-pprod/o-pagamento-da-fatura.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689390-pbig/o-pagamento-da-fatura.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7301]]></id><name><![CDATA[totloyaltyadvanced]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Loyalty Program - 1.5, 1.6 & 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fidelização & Apadrinhamento]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This is the best module for customer rewards points! Customize the number of points awarded for each product or each client : add, modify or delete points manually]]></description><author><![CDATA[202 ecommerce]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/fidelizacao-apadrinhamento/7301-advanced-loyalty-program-15-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7301.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This is the best module for customer rewards points! Customize the number of points awarded for each product or each client : add, modify or delete points manually.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can now highlight products by assigning a number of loyalty points to each product according to the price, or by fixed amount.In addition, you can list clients who have accumulated the most points.Finally, you can assign points manually. This will be useful if you want to thank a customer.New! You can edit and delete a number of loyalty points assigned to a customer, you can also see the history of his loyalty points. For exemple, in case of technical problems you can correct the number of points.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/836669-pprod/advanced-loyalty-program-15-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/836669-pbig/advanced-loyalty-program-15-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price Increment/Reduction by group, category and more]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Promoções & Brindes]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With our module you can set the product prices to your customers which do you want to really have]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/promocoes-brindes/7422-price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With our module you can set the product prices to your customers which do you want to really have.&nbsp;Increments, reductions (discounts) and massive fixed price changes with an unlimited conditions and combinations to modify your product prices.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Change the product prices massivelyYou can change the price of the products massively, setting an increment, a discount or a fixed price using these conditions:- Category- Product- Customer group- Customer- Country- Zone- Supplier- Manufacturer- Language- Currency&nbsp;If you choose the percentage type, it can be calculated from Retail or Wholesale price and with or without taxes.To apply the rule, you have this additional controls:&nbsp;- Minimum threshold price- Maximum threshold price- Date From- Date To&nbsp;And also, you can control the final price result setting a minimum and a maximum price with:&nbsp;- Minimum result price- Maximum result price&nbsp;The module adds a priority system in case that two or more rules must be applied to the same product. In this case, you can establish a priority to set the order and if you want to only execute one of this rules (using the option:&quot;Apply only one condition&quot;).&nbsp;&nbsp;Discounts managementTo apply and manage the discounts with our module, you have 3 options:&nbsp;- Show reduction as discount: With this option enabled, the reduction is showed like discount (specific price), then the price of the product will show the old price and the new price with the discount amount/percentage.* Only works if the rule configuration create with our module is a discount.&nbsp;- Skip other discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will not be applied to this product.- Override discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will be applied and the previous discount will be overrided (ommitted but not deleted).This 2 options, are applicable with any of the configurations that you can do with our module.&nbsp;Examples of using the module:- Very useful for the promotions season like Black Friday, Sales, Christmas, Cyber Monday, etc... to change the prices in the products with begin and end date activating and deactivating the offer automatically.- You can set an increment in the catalog products only or a currency (or currencies) to avoid the currency conversion losses.- Set a reduction for a VIP customers group offering them more competitives prices or set an increment to your Resellers group to get more benefits from the products.- Change the prices in a Country or Zone and promote the sales in this geographical area.&nbsp;* The module doesn&#39;t change the original price of the product (you never will lose the original price).&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Attributes filter (combinations)With the new attributes filter you can set the price changes only for an specific product combination.Example: Modify the price only of your product with the L and XL size and not for the prices of the S and M size.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Features filterWith the new features filter you can set the price changes only for products with an specific feature.Example: Modify the price only for the cotton and synthetic products.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Quantity product units filterAdded a new field to set the m&iacute;nimum quantity units of the product that must be in the cart to apply the change in the price.Example: Modify the price of product from 3 units, then, the price of product will be changed automatically only if 3 or more products are added to the cart.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Change the prices within a period (date from and date to)Configure the price changes (increment, discount or fixed price) between 2 dates, or from a date or until a date. It&#39;s an optional field, is not necessary to set a date, if 0 there&#39;s no period limit to apply the rule.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20 until 2016-10-30Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) until 2016-10-30.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Threshold prices to apply the rulesApply the change in your prices only for the product which price is between a threshold.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 10&euro; and less than 30&euro;.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 50&euro;.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is less than 100&euro;.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Minimum and maximum result priceNow, you can set a minimum and a maximum price to get if the result of the increment or discount is below or above this prices.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 200If the result price after the rule application is below 100&euro; (89&euro; for example), the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is above 200&euro; (205&euro; for example) the product price will be 200&euro;.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 0If the result price after the rule application is below 100&euro; (89&euro; for example), the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is 105&euro; the product price will be 105&euro;.Example: Minimum result price = 0 and Maximum result price 100If the result price after the rule application is above 100&euro; (105&euro; for example) the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is 80&euro; the product price will be 80&euro;.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Category tree to select the categoriesNew friendly interface in the Categories selector. Now, the display is in a category tree to select the categories easily.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Friendly multiple selectors interfaceNew friendly multiple selector interface with add and remove buttons and a search box.&nbsp;&nbsp;Geolocation compatibilityFull compatibility with Prestashop Geolocation to change the prices by Zone and Country. If the customer is not logged and the Prestashop Geolocation is enabled, the prices will be shown by the geolocation IP Country of the customer.If logged, the country and the zone calculation is done from the address delivery.&nbsp;&nbsp;Apply a markup or offer a discount in your productsFeel free to play with a markup in the price of your products creating an increment or a reduction configuration by category, by product, by customer group, by customer, by country, by zone, by supplier and by manufacturer.&nbsp;Example: You can create a new category, associate the products to this category and with our module you could set all this category products to 20$ without changing the original product price and without creating complicated discount rules to obtain the desired price.&nbsp;&nbsp;No multistore needed for the same catalog productsThe customers group filter allows to avoid creating a multistore for a B2B and B2C store, sharing the same catalog products but with different prices in each.&nbsp;&nbsp;Our guarantees&nbsp;✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote.&nbsp;Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812413-pprod/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812413-pbig/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7484]]></id><name><![CDATA[newsletterpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Boletim informativo & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/boletim-informativo-sms/7484-newsletter-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7484.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that advertising plays a key role in promoting any business. Using our newsletter will boost your sales faster and easier than any other newsletter module available on the market. This module is an easy and fast way to send customizable newsletters about top selling products or special offers to your clients.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/724699-pprod/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724699-pbig/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law (Notification Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Jurídico]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/juridico/8734-eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The only module that allows you to fully comply with the EU cookie law. Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module fully complies with the European Cookie Law.  Complete compliance with the law  Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information."  Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will.  Main features of the modulesDisplay a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consentDisable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.Fully customize the warning banner (color, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency, buttons...) Getting the user consent   The module includes 2 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled. We recommend you to use this mode, this one allows you to fully comply with the law.Acceptance through the navigation: If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled.Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months)  Customizing the banner content and design  As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store).  The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, color, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background color of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is multilingual and automatically detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language.  Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots crawl you store in order not to affect your SEO.  Disabling the modules that use cookies  This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookies on their computer with their consent.  "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law  To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents.  Multistore mode  The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.5.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pprod/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689395-pbig/eu-cookie-law-notification-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8741]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmulistecommandes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Improved Order List]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gerenciamento de pedidos]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/gerenciamento-pedidos/8741-dmu-improved-order-list.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8741.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The more orders you have to process, the more this module will save you time. As much by the fact that all information is available from the order list and because you will be able to change status in mass with this module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/740079-pprod/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/740079-pbig/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8895]]></id><name><![CDATA[freedeliverymanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Free Delivery Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Custo de frete]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/custo-de-frete/8895-free-delivery-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8895.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction. According to the rules you have chosen, you encourage customers to increase the value of their purchases in order to take advantage of free delivery.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Developing your sales by increasing the value of transactions has never been an easy thing to implement. The “Free Delivery Manager” module is actually the perfect solution for offering your respected customers free shipping through objective rules. It is the promise of a rise in the amount of orders with total control of delivery costs.  The module allows you to calculate in advance, with the help of precise rules, the necessary conditions for unlocking free delivery. The management and monitoring are done according to carriers, delivery area, price, weight, or any other criteria you term as important for your business.  The “Free Delivery Manager” module offers control of delivery costs by releasing delivery available as a function of criteria you have chosen. All the carriers have their own price list. You may, for example, indicate a minimum order amount by carrier In presenting to the customer, in their order summary, the amount remaining before delivery is available, so you definitely encourage them to order more.  Highly detailed statistics visually present two types of reports together. The first one presents the number of orders that have benefited from free delivery, as well as the total and per-order amount that this cost you. You really control the impact of delivery costs. The second report displays the detail of costs caused by free postage and the orders where the rules for free shipping are applied. Thus, the “Free Delivery Manager” module increases the value of transactions as well as the number of orders!  This module has been constantly evolving, many thanks to user feedback. TimActive, in fact, grants great importance to your perception of our solutions and of the improvements that can be added. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/691962-pprod/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691962-pbig/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8934]]></id><name><![CDATA[migrationpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[MigrationPro: Prestashop to Prestashop Migration Tool]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Migração de Dados & Registro]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Upgrade PrestaShop or Migrating data between PrestaShops.MigrationPro is safe, easy and wicked fast automated module for upgrade PrestaShop and PrestaShop to PrestaShop migration tool]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/migracao-dados-registro/8934-migrationpro-prestashop-to-prestashop-migration-tool.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8934.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Upgrade PrestaShop or Migrating data between PrestaShops.MigrationPro is safe, easy and wicked fast automated module for upgrade PrestaShop and PrestaShop to PrestaShop migration tool.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[What is it for? PrestaShop is one of the fast improvement eCommerce platforms at the current time and future. The MigrationPro helps You upgrade old PrestaShop to new featured version and being innovative on your eCommerce business without important data loss. The module also can migrate part of a data to other PrestaShop. e.g. You can share products or customers with other PrestaShop.  The best solution for migration data from old PrestaShop to clean PrestaShop! How to use?MigrationPro is very understandable and has the useful interface for configuration such complex operations. Just the module designed for the Merchants.  How does it work?Usually, data migration process is a very laborious process and responsible. Migration process goes in the background between your carts server with sending HTTP requests and AJAX methods.  It is too safe than we know and wicked fast.  Why is MigrationPro?MigrationPro has been the #1 selling PrestaShop migration module on the whole market.  MigrationPro developed by the team of experts with the 5 years experiences on PrestaShop to PrestaShop data migration procedure. We have developed an intelligent transportation of the data. Excellent reviews from Merchants are evidence of our professionalism. Assiduous Support. Real Time. Real People. We know what it’s like to need support. Our philosophy is to treat you as we would like to be treated. It’s no wonder that some of our best reviews are about our amazing support. Time. Our time has started the countdown. Not in our power to stop time. This module helps to save your time for more important things. "To do the migration manually on each product will take 15 minutes from your life. For 1,000 product you will spend about 30 days. MigrationPro will do less than 10 minutes." It's really wicked fast!  :) Buy now and Save Your time! We have no limit....Unlimited data migrationsUnlimited uses for re-migration and upgrade PrestaShop to the last stable version.Included plugins:Multi-store shops migration pluginCustomer Password migration pluginSEO URLs migrations plugin It is time to make your life easy. Get the MigrationPro in action!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[migration_tools]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/797205-pprod/migrationpro-prestashop-to-prestashop-migration-tool.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/797205-pbig/migrationpro-prestashop-to-prestashop-migration-tool.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Vendas cruzadas & Pacotes de produtos]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumente facilmente o valor m&eacute;dio do carrinho oferecendo descontos personalizados aos seus clientes no resumo do carrinho de compras]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/vendas-cruzadas-pacotes-produtos/11345-push-on-cart.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumente facilmente o valor m&eacute;dio do carrinho oferecendo descontos personalizados aos seus clientes no resumo do carrinho de compras.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[O m&oacute;dulo Push on Cart permite:&nbsp;Aumentar facilmente o valor m&eacute;dio do carrinho dos clientes&nbsp;Limpar o estoque de produtos n&atilde;o vendidos selecionadosAjudar os clientes a descobrir novos produtos e criar uma demandaAumentar a satisfa&ccedil;&atilde;o e a fidelidade dos clientes com descontos personalizados em produtos selecionados]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.13]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/push-on-cart.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/push-on-cart.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[RockPOS - Ponto de Venda e Omnicanal]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Software de caixa (POS)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Graças ao RockPOS, sendo o proprietário de uma loja online, pode agora vender em espaços físicos]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/software-de-caixa-pos/13654-rockpos-ponto-de-venda-e-omnicanal.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Graças ao RockPOS, sendo o proprietário de uma loja online, pode agora vender em espaços físicos. O RockPOS mantém um omnicanal de vendas sob controlo, ao possibilitar uma sincronização de 2 vias e atualizações em tempo real das suas transações]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Vendas pelo omnicanalO RockPOS ajuda a ligar as suas lojas online com as físicas e permite que controle [o] seu negócio em diferentes canais usando apenas um sistema. Ao sincronizar produtos, encomendas ou clientes, pode ver todas as transações em todos os canais,num só lugar e ao mesmo tempo, o que lhe iria  poupar tempo e esforço, para além de melhorar a sua experiência com os clientes. Por exemplo, atualizações de stock em tempo real permitem que saiba se há stockde sobra ou não, suficiente para fazer outro pedido. Diminui o processo de verificaçãoNão gostaria de “servir rápido para servir mais” em vez de gastar demasiado tempo a fazer um pedido ou encomenda? Agora pode completar uma encomenda com apenas alguns cliques, graças ao design simples e fácil de usar do RockPOS. Além disso, o RockPOS também pode ser ligadoa vários aparelhos de hardware (por exemplo: scanners de códigos de barra, impressoras de recibos, etc.) para fazer as transações ocorrerem rapidamente e sem problemas. Agora também é capaz de permitir que os clientes devolvam/troquem produtos se quiserem. Não só as encomendasdevolvidas serão registadas, como o stock também será atualizado automaticamente. Economize dinheiro e tempoGerir uma loja online e física pode agora ser feito com apenas 1 sistema, porque o RockPOS fez como se um módulo embutido no seu back office. Compre apenas uma vez e poderá usá-lo para o resto da sua vida sem nenhuma taxa extra. Não é necessário softwares extras nem nenhuma formação especial porque o RockPOS foi desenvolvido para ser um POS completo, com design fácil e simples, para que qualquer um possa usá-lo com facilidade. Precisará de no máximo 30 minutos para se treinar a si mesmo e os seus funcionários sobre como usar o RockPOS, e eles ficarão confiantes para servir os clientes.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[299.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[359.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[269.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/884358-pprod/rockpos-ponto-de-venda-e-omnicanal.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/884358-pbig/rockpos-ponto-de-venda-e-omnicanal.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[cartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Reativação de Carrinho Abandonado]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Compras abandonados]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Melhore a taxa de fechamento em mais de 15% gra&ccedil;as aos e-mails de lembrete de carrinhos abandonados e ofere&ccedil;a inclusive desconto para incentivar ainda mais o cliente a fechar!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/remarketing-compras-abandonados/16535-reativacao-de-carrinho-abandonado.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Melhore a taxa de fechamento em mais de 15% gra&ccedil;as aos e-mails de lembrete de carrinhos abandonados e ofere&ccedil;a inclusive desconto para incentivar ainda mais o cliente a fechar!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatize em alguns cliques o envio de e-mail de reativa&ccedil;&atilde;o de carrinho abandonado.Adicione facilmente um desconto (ou frete gr&aacute;tis) na mensagem, conforme o valor do carrinho, para otimizar os fechamentos.Maximize o incentivo enviando 1, 2 ou 3 lembretes quando desejar, e nos idiomas que quiser.Aproveite o intuitivo, facilmente configur&aacute;vel e totalmente personaliz&aacute;vel com as cores de sua loja. N&atilde;o perca mais clientes hesitantes! Crie rapidamente e-mails autom&aacute;ticos para reativar os carrinhos que n&atilde;o resultaram em venda.  Coment&aacute;rios: Postado em 30/08/2014 &ndash; ID do pedido:&nbsp;﻿#232568 &ldquo;o melhor m&oacute;dulo que comprei na Prestashop: f&aacute;cil de instalar e usar, fant&aacute;stico!&rdquo;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.25]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[134.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[94.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/920927-pprod/reativacao-de-carrinho-abandonado.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/920927-pbig/reativacao-de-carrinho-abandonado.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (Referenciamento natural)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumente o tr&aacute;fego do site aparecendo na primeira p&aacute;gina dos resultados dos motores de busca!  Este m&oacute;dulo SEO Expert preenche automaticamente as metatags e as metatags de m&iacute]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/seo-referenciamento-natural/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumente o tr&aacute;fego do site aparecendo na primeira p&aacute;gina dos resultados dos motores de busca!  Este m&oacute;dulo SEO Expert preenche automaticamente as metatags e as metatags de m&iacute;dia social para otimizar sua loja online para melhor visibilidade nos motores de busca e plataformas de m&iacute;dia social.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Crie metatags automaticamente poupando mais de 40 horas!  Com o m&oacute;dulo SEO Expert voc&ecirc;:aparece na primeira p&aacute;gina de resultados de motores de busca como Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.multiplica suas vendas com aumento de tr&aacute;fego na webmelhora a visibilidade de cada idioma de sua lojaaumenta as suas convers&otilde;es gra&ccedil;as a tr&aacute;fego qualificadodiferencia sua loja com regras totalmente personalizadas para p&aacute;ginas de produtos e categoriasaproveita o Facebook e Twitter para conseguir ainda mais clientesotimiza sua loja online para a m&iacute;dia social com t&iacute;tulos compartilhados adaptadosAproveite a oportunidade para compr&aacute;-lo a pre&ccedil;o de lan&ccedil;amento!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[179.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pprod/seo-expert.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pbig/seo-expert.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17545]]></id><name><![CDATA[veplatform]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ve | Converta carrinhos abandonados]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Compras abandonados]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A única solução de marketing automatizada para resolver seus problemas de abandono e conversão em cada etapa do funil de compras]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/remarketing-compras-abandonados/17545-ve-converta-carrinhos-abandonados.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17545.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A única solução de marketing automatizada para resolver seus problemas de abandono e conversão em cada etapa do funil de compras. Comece utilizar a Ve hoje gratuitamente por 30 dias!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[O Problema: 98% dos visitantes do seu site não estão comprando de você. Além disso, o abandono do carrinho de compras é a razão de 3 a 4 de seus potenciais clientes não estarem comprando. Como a Ve resolve isso? Engaja com usuários que estão prestes a sair do siteRe-engaja com clientes perdidos e os traz de volta ao seu siteAumenta a receita do seu siteMelhora a experiência onsite do seu cliente Benefícios da Ve: Transforma visitantes passivos em clientes - e engaja com visitantes no seu site uma vez que eles o deixaramFácil de usar - configuração simples, manutenção e modelo de preços transparente (pague sobre performance - você só paga quando os clientes convertem).Soluções baseadas em dados - nossas percepções sobre o comportamento do cliente nos ajudam a entregar a mensagem certa no momento certo.Gerenciamento de marca centralizado e campanhas personalizáveis ​​- faça o upload de seu logotipo e fonte para consistência da marca, altere a cópia e a mensagem de acordo com a campanha.Crescerá com o seu negócio - aproveite os recursos novos e aprimorados conforme sua empresa cresce.FAQs abrangentes - aproveite a nossa experiência. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[17.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/783997-pprod/ve-converta-carrinhos-abandonados.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/783997-pbig/ve-converta-carrinhos-abandonados.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18656]]></id><name><![CDATA[jmarketplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[JA Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Criação de Marketplace]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/criacao-marketplace/18656-ja-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18656.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Best module of Spain in PrestaShop Awards 2015.  This module allows you to integrate several shops in the same economic platform and common retail space. All members can benefit from the sales force other vendors to obtain greater visibility increasing the number of customers and sales.  This integration of sale is currently one of the most effective ways to compete with traditional large surfaces and large ecommerce operators (Amazon, eBay, etc.).  With this module you can join in their market strength of different suppliers to have more visibility and more sales. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.8.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[239.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/717058-pprod/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/717058-pbig/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18850]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderedit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Order Edit - Change and Modify existing order]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gerenciamento de pedidos]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With this module you can modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/gerenciamento-pedidos/18850-order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18850.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With this module you can modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Articles information, shipping information, payments and discounts can be modified. Please refer to the screens, the video, the demoshop, or contact us directly in order to get more information on how the module works.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/714564-pprod/order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/714564-pbig/order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18921]]></id><name><![CDATA[mailchimp]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Mailchimp Newsletter & Statistics - 1.6 & 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Boletim informativo & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Gerencie facilmente seus boletins informativos com o m&oacute;dulo MailChimp Oficial que permite projetar, enviar e acompanhar suas campanhas pelo seu Back Office PrestaShop!&nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/boletim-informativo-sms/18921-mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18921.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Gerencie facilmente seus boletins informativos com o m&oacute;dulo MailChimp Oficial que permite projetar, enviar e acompanhar suas campanhas pelo seu Back Office PrestaShop!&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo MailChimp Oficial: &nbsp;Crie boletins informativos totalmente personaliz&aacute;veis &agrave; imagem de sua loja;Programe seus boletins informativos com um clique;Fidelize seus clientes importando suas listas de cadastrados pelo MailChimp e informando-lhes suas promo&ccedil;&otilde;es e outras not&iacute;cias;Atualize a qualquer momento as listas de cadastrados com os novos clientes em sua loja;Segmente os destinat&aacute;rios para fazer campanhas mais personalizadas (clientes que clicaram num boletim informativo, etc.);Acompanhe seus boletins confortavelmente no seu back-office PrestaShop gra&ccedil;as &agrave;s estat&iacute;sticas avan&ccedil;adas;Simplifique sua vida: todas as interfaces do m&oacute;dulo est&atilde;o totalmente traduzidas!O MailChimp j&aacute; &eacute; utilizado por mais de 7 milh&otilde;es de usu&aacute;rios, n&atilde;o espere mais para us&aacute;-lo! &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[144.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[99.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pprod/mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/645020-pbig/mailchimp-newsletter-statistics-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19062]]></id><name><![CDATA[layerslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Layer Slider - Responsive SlideShow]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Sliders & Galerias]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[LayerSlider is a premium multi-purpose slider to create image galleries, content sliders, and mind-blowing slideshows with must-see effects]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/sliders-galerias/19062-layer-slider-responsive-slideshow.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19062.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[LayerSlider is a premium multi-purpose slider to create image galleries, content sliders, and mind-blowing slideshows with must-see effects. It uses cutting edge technologies to provide the smoothest experience that&rsquo;s possible. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Layer Slider comes with more than 200 preset 2D and 3D slide transitions. It has a beautiful and easy-to-use admin interface with supporting modern features like drag &#39;n&rsquo; drop WYSIWYG slider builder, real-time previews, timeline view, Google Fonts and transition builder for custom animations. It&rsquo;s device friendly by supporting responsive mode, multiple layouts, touch gestures on mobile devices, and uses techniques like lazy load and conditional script loading for optimal performance. You can add any content into sliders, including images, text, custom HTML, YouTube and Vimeo videos or HTML5 self-hosted multimedia contents. It&rsquo;s also SEO friendly by allowing you to build semantic markup with custom attributes that search engines can index easily. LayerSlider comes with 13 built-in skins, and it hastons of options to entirely customize the appearance and behavior of your sliders at the smallest detail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.1.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/726345-pprod/layer-slider-responsive-slideshow.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/726345-pbig/layer-slider-responsive-slideshow.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19431]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestanotifypro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pop Promo (Popup)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiplique a efic&aacute;cia de suas promo&ccedil;&otilde;es!  Com esse pop-in, configur&aacute;vel em menos de um minuto, atraia imediatamente a aten&ccedil;&atilde;o dos visitantes para aquilo que ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pop-up/19431-pop-promo-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19431.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiplique a efic&aacute;cia de suas promo&ccedil;&otilde;es!  Com esse pop-in, configur&aacute;vel em menos de um minuto, atraia imediatamente a aten&ccedil;&atilde;o dos visitantes para aquilo que voc&ecirc; deseja, tornando bem-sucedidas suas promo&ccedil;&otilde;es, liquida&ccedil;&otilde;es e vendas instant&acirc;neas.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Aumente de 20% a 1.000% seu &iacute;ndice de convers&atilde;o em promo&ccedil;&otilde;es, bem como as assinaturas do boletim informativoGaranta o sucesso do lan&ccedil;amento de seus novos produtos tornando-os imperd&iacute;veisBasta um minuto para configurar esse m&oacute;dulo. Assim, &eacute; poss&iacute;vel faz&ecirc;-lo a qualquer momento ou programar campanhas com anteced&ecirc;nciaQueime facilmente seus estoques com promo&ccedil;&otilde;es especiais para algum item encalhado, abrindo espa&ccedil;o para as novas cole&ccedil;&otilde;es]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/663202-pprod/pop-promo-popup.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/663202-pbig/pop-promo-popup.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19584]]></id><name><![CDATA[tacartreminder]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Smart Cart Reminder]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Compras abandonados]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/remarketing-compras-abandonados/19584-smart-cart-reminder.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19584.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it. The advanced solution for the abandoned cart reminder is what will fit your reminder emails, your promotions to your customers' cart.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[According to the abandoned cart content, and information about the customers, the Smart Cart Reminder module is the advanced solution that allows you to remind your abandoned carts in an autonomous and focused way.  « The only module of the cart reminder without subscription offering as many features »  ** EMAILS OF REMINDER AND OFFERS ABOUT MARKETING ADAPTED TO EACH CART ** Indeed, the module allows you to create "Reminder rules" according to:Customer information (country, age, gender, group, etc.)Cart contents (amount, products, product categories, stock remaining, etc.)Time of year (Christmas, New Year’s, Valentine’s Day, Mothers’ Day, etc.) « No more untimely and inappropriate promotions which let you feel that you are desperate ! »  With the reminder rules, create easily your own algorithms, for example:  Rule 1 : For the cart that exceeds $90, which still contain available items in my stock, the customer is in USA. Then create a discount coupon to obtain the shipping costs for free. Reminder1: Send the « Free shipping costs » email. Reminder2: Send the « Only a few days to benefit from the offer» email. ------------ Rule 2: For the new customers, create a 5% Off Your Order. Reminder1: 1H after the dropped cart: send the «To celebrate your arrival 5% Off Your First Order » email. Reminder2: 24H after Reminder 1: send the « Only one day left to take advantage of this offer» email. ------------ Rule 3: From 15/11/2015 to 25/12/2015(Christmas time), create a coupon to obtain a gift on the order. Reminder 1: Send the « Surprise Gift» email. Reminder 2: Send the « Only a few days to benefit from the offer» email. ------------ Rule 4: For the cart > €900, the customer is professional Reminder 1: Send the « More information about our catalog dedicated to professional» email. Reminder 2: Contact the customer by phone  My interest through Smart Cart Reminder module and the reminder rules: →  I increase my sales →  I control the cost of my marketing offers according to the cart →  I approach as close as possible to the desire of my customers →  I gain credibility by creating an intelligent and autonomous system which is no longer seen by my customers as an automatic emails or promotion distributor.   ** MANY KINDS OF REMINDER « STANDARD» or «MANUAL» ** Two kinds of reminders to adapt a little more to your reminder process:«Standard»: Sending an automatic email with a custom content of the cart to the customer.« Manual»: The module notifies you by email to communicate with the customer.You can even set the type of reminder that will suit your cart.   ** AN INTERFACE DEDICATED TO  « MANUAL » REMINDERS (PHONE) ** In one page, the module includes all the information of your customers; and includes many features dedicated for your manual reminders.  My interest through my module « Smart Cart Reminder » and its page dedicated for manual reminders: →  I don’t lose anymore my customers information enabling me converting ( phone number, address, page visited, number of orders placed, current cart …) → I win in reactivity through the features present in this unique page: Sending a Pre-formatted email with the link of the complete order, creation of good (s) reduction (s) → I comment all my telephone conversations   ** ADVANCED STATISTICS **  The module provides a group of advanced reports easy-to-understand:The evolution of the generated sales according to cart remindersReports about the opened/clicked emailsCart reminder rule conversion reportsReports on employees manually remind customers. This report contains the number of orders made, the number of manual reminder processed for each employee. My interest through statistics is to improve me reminder system: →  I improve my reminder emails to convert the maximum of cart →  I improve my rules to build an autonomous system →  I motivate my employees to increase my sales   ** AN INTUITIVE AND EASY MODULE TO TAKE IN CHARGE **  « A quick start: Coming from a study conducted in the comb to a Committee of a dozen merchants, the module provides a clear and pleasant interface to use. Because we are committed to place the e-trader at the center of the process when we design our modules»  The module provides a range of features allowing you to act directly on the abandoned cart, you can manually raise without even that the countdown is finished, see explicit details of the choice of a rule for a cart...  My interest through its intuitive and transparent interface    I spot in one glance: → The rules applied on the cart on each abandoned cart → The time left before the next reminder through the countdown → The list of reminders applied on the cart → If the reminder email was been seen and clicked → If the order was completed →  ...   ** AN OPERATIONAL MODULE IN SOME CLICKS! **  1 Installation in 1 click and intuitive setting in 2 steps:1. I created my reminder emails, it’s easy and fast! Several templates of emails delivered with the module, customize easily and quickly, select an example, edit the colors, edit the text, and here we go! 2- I create my cart reminder rules and I indicate for each rule the reminder emails to send.  ** A SUPPORT AT YOUR SERVICE **«Because your time is precious and that we want your full satisfaction! »  You have particular difficulty for the integration, you have some questions. Our team will be glad to support you. We are very sensitive about the responsiveness and the quality of our responses.   Source « addons.prestashop.com »:  From 09/2013 to 08/2015  Tickets received: 362 Handled: 362 Our overall service quality: 99.7% ** THEY BOUGHT THE MODULE AND YOU?**  20/08/2015 «Your module is terrific!!! »  15/08/2015 - 5/5 «Great module and great support! »  28/07/2015 - 5/5 Lots of options to help increase sales. Very friendly and responsive customer service. Highly recommended!  15/07/2015 - 5/5 Very good quality, congratulation.  « I tried the challenge and I am pleased, congratulations to the developers of this module.  I like your system customizing email, this is top! » Cathy  « I'm a merchant since 8 years ago, and I gave some ideas. In fact I wanted a new condition to treat new customers differently and according to my stock. A module that I don’t leave no more! What flexibility! I paid the purchase in the first week. » Audrey« Don’t hesitate to share with us your comments!»]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.22]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[179.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pprod/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pbig/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19749]]></id><name><![CDATA[flashsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Premium Flash Sale]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Vendas Privadas & Vendas Ultrarrápidas]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiply your shop sales using Flash Sales! Customisable and ideal for generating impulse buys, the Premium Flash Sales module increases your conversion rate and allows easy destocking]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/vendas-privadas-vendas-ultrarrapidas/19749-premium-flash-sale.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19749.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiply your shop sales using Flash Sales! Customisable and ideal for generating impulse buys, the Premium Flash Sales module increases your conversion rate and allows easy destocking. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your transformation rate by up to 59% thanks to flash sales!Boost your sales by giving your offers maximum visibilityLiquidate your stocks quickly and effectively to economise on storage costsLiven up your online shop easily and encourage your visitors to return to your store regularlyEncourage your indecisive customers to complete their purchases quickly because of the very limited duration of the offer and the countdown&nbsp; &nbsp; Expert tip: Send a newsletter to your customers to tell them about your flash sales using Official MailChimp (56% of businesses say they have a higher newsletter opening rate during flash sale periods) or inform your visitors when they reach your site thanks to a Pop Promo!  Comment posted on&nbsp;2015-11-05 09:51:48: &quot;Great! Works perfectly&quot; F. CASOLARI]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/905699-pprod/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/905699-pbig/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20541]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalbrazilianregister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cadastro Brasileiro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cadastro e Processo de Pedido]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Este módulo adiciona os campos opcionais ou obrigatórios de CPF, CNPJ, Inscrição Estadual (IE) e RG no cadastro dos clientes da sua loja online]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/cadastro-e-processo-de-pedido/20541-cadastro-brasileiro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20541.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Este módulo adiciona os campos opcionais ou obrigatórios de CPF, CNPJ, Inscrição Estadual (IE) e RG no cadastro dos clientes da sua loja online. Também busca e preenche um endereço completo com o CEP e tem máscara do padrão brasileiro de telefone.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[O comerciante tem um controle total sobre as informações que serão pedidas ao cliente. Ele pode configurar o CPF e o CNPJ como informações obrigatórias ou não. O módulo vai verificar se o CPF ou o CNPJ informados são corretos e os clientes não podem se cadastrar colocando um CPF ou CNPJ errado. Essas informações devem ser confiáveis para a emissão de notas fiscais.  O CEP pode ser usado para obter o endereço completo. Caso o cliente não conheça seu CEP, o comerciante tem a possibilidade de exibir um botão “Não sei meu CEP”, para auxiliá-lo com a ajuda do site dos correios.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/704295-pprod/cadastro-brasileiro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/704295-pbig/cadastro-brasileiro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21273]]></id><name><![CDATA[pqeasypost]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Post Pro (DHL, GLS, DPD, Colissimo, RoyalMail etc)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Preparação & Remessa]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/preparacao-remessa/21273-easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21273.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost.com API (Application Programming Interface) into PrestaShop and printing your shipping labels fast and easy. Only 3 cents per label!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that in order to run a successful business you have to optimize it and automatize it as much as possible, this module allows you to do that by increasing the shipping process by 70%.   Think of how long it takes to receive an order from your customers, process the order by adding the products to the package, then connect to your shipping carrier`s software and manually insert the customer information, parcel information and delivery address for the order, for each order at a time. This is very time consuming and it`s very easy to make mistakes because you have a lot of data to process.  With this module all of this is done automatically via the API (Application Programming Interface) that connects the orders section in prestashop with the carrier and instantly sends the information to the carrier, then prints the shipping label which is then slicked to the package. The module supports the most important carriers in the world.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[119.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/726515-pprod/easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/726515-pbig/easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21278]]></id><name><![CDATA[popnewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Popup Newsletter]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A forma mais eficaz de manter-se em contato com seus clientes!   Pop Newsletter cria um pop-up convidando seus visitantes a assinar sua newsletter]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pop-up/21278-popup-newsletter.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21278.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A forma mais eficaz de manter-se em contato com seus clientes!   Pop Newsletter cria um pop-up convidando seus visitantes a assinar sua newsletter. Com este pop-up profissional e completamente personaliz&aacute;vel, voc&ecirc; pode atrair novos assinantes e ret&ecirc;-los com um desconto para a pr&oacute;xima compra.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Pop Newsletter permite que voc&ecirc; mostre aos seus visitantes um pop-in quando eles chegarem em sua loja. Transforme seus visitantes em assinantes! &nbsp; Aumente a taxa de assinatura para sua loja:&nbsp; Os pop-ins s&atilde;o eficazes atraindo a aten&ccedil;&atilde;o dos visitantes, ganhando mais cliques do que barras deslizantes, banners ou pain&eacute;is de assinatura no rodap&eacute; (que t&ecirc;m uma taxa de convers&atilde;o de apenas 0,05%). Os resultados comprovados desta ferramenta mostram aumentos ente 20% e 1.000% em sua taxa de assinatura. &nbsp; Transforme seus assinantes em clientes fi&eacute;is: Ofere&ccedil;a a eles um cupom de desconto para a pr&oacute;xima compra em sua loja como agradecimento por terem assinado a newsletter. &nbsp; Ofere&ccedil;a uma experi&ecirc;ncia do usu&aacute;rio perfeita: Similares aos pop-ups mas com uma experi&ecirc;ncia do usu&aacute;rio aprimorada, os pop-ins integram-se perfeitamente &agrave; p&aacute;gina quando aparecem. Pop Newsletter aplica as melhores pr&aacute;ticas recomendadas para este m&eacute;todo de propaganda:O efeito lightboxOp&ccedil;&atilde;o de fechar a janela do m&oacute;dulo com um simples clique fora do pop-in, al&eacute;m de um bot&atilde;o com um s&iacute;mbolo de cruz para fechamento no canto superior direito.Op&ccedil;&atilde;o para especificar quando o pop-in &eacute; ativado. Isso permite ao seu visitante conhecer o seu site antes de ver o pop-in.Quando seu visitante fechar o pop-in, ele n&atilde;o ser&aacute; mostrado novamente.Adapt&aacute;vel a todos os tipos de loja, sem necessidade de conhecimentos de programa&ccedil;&atilde;o ou design gr&aacute;fico.&nbsp; Melhore os resultados de suas newsletters aumentando o seu banco de contatos: Gra&ccedil;as ao formul&aacute;rio opcional de assinatura da newsletter, voc&ecirc; pode analisar e classificar seus assinantes de forma mais eficaz. Pop Newsletter tamb&eacute;m permite que voc&ecirc; envie uma confirma&ccedil;&atilde;o por e-mail ao endere&ccedil;o de e-mail fornecido pelo seu assinante para garantir que sua newsletter chegue no endere&ccedil;o correto.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/722395-pprod/popup-newsletter.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/722395-pbig/popup-newsletter.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21510]]></id><name><![CDATA[popexit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pop Exit - Pop-up de retargeting no site]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pop-up]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[No momento em que os visitantes estiverem saindo do seu site, fa&ccedil;a com que uma janela pop-up apare&ccedil;a para motiv&aacute;-los a finalizar o pedido!  O m&oacute;dulo Pop Exit permite trazer]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pop-up/21510-pop-exit-pop-up-de-retargeting-no-site.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21510.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[No momento em que os visitantes estiverem saindo do seu site, fa&ccedil;a com que uma janela pop-up apare&ccedil;a para motiv&aacute;-los a finalizar o pedido!  O m&oacute;dulo Pop Exit permite trazer de volta 25% dos internautas que estiverem deixando o site, propondo um desconto tempor&aacute;rio (ou permanente) bastante atrativo.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Reduza os carrinhos abandonados detendo os visitantes quando estiverem saindo do site e motivando-os a concluir a compra;Aumente a taxa de convers&atilde;o da sua loja oferecendo aos visitantes um desconto tempor&aacute;rio para encoraj&aacute;-los a comprar;Integre ao site uma ferramenta de retargeting eficaz e atrativa em menos de 5 minutos por meio dos designs profissionais dispon&iacute;veis e o m&oacute;dulo de f&aacute;cil configura&ccedil;&atilde;o.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/727469-pprod/pop-exit-pop-up-de-retargeting-no-site.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/727469-pbig/pop-exit-pop-up-de-retargeting-no-site.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21829]]></id><name><![CDATA[djtalcorreios]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cálculo do frete pelos Correios]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Transportadoras]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[“Cálculo do frete pelos Correios” é um módulo completamente configurável que considera peso, deslocamento e regras do lojista para frete grátis]]></description><author><![CDATA[BM Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/transportadoras/21829-calculo-do-frete-pelos-correios.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21829.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[“Cálculo do frete pelos Correios” é um módulo completamente configurável que considera peso, deslocamento e regras do lojista para frete grátis. Usamos tecnologia dos correios e integramos todo o processo no checkout e carrinho PrestaShop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Tenha total controle sobre o sistema de cálculo de frete exibido para seu cliente. A integração no carrinho e checkout PrestaShop é clara, porém não intrusiva. Poupe tempo do seu atendimento ao cliente.Cálculo do valor e prazo do frete – SEDEX, E-SEDEX, PAC e SEDEX a Cobrar.Calculo integrado com PrestaShop – O peso do seu produto no cadastro PrestaShop é levado em consideração para fazer os cálculos do frete.Regras para frete grátis – O lojista pode, opcionalmente, estabelecer faixas de preço mínimo e máximo para o carrinho aonde o frete é gratuito.Tecnologia dos Correios – Você pode confiar que nossos resultados batem com o que você encontrará nos correios.Configuração completa – O “Cálculo do frete pelos Correios” foi pensado para atender suas necessidades de configuração e ser uma verdadeira ferramenta para o lojista.Redução da carga de trabalho do atendimento ao consumidor – Os próprios clientes fazem seus cálculos de frete.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[144.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/732590-pprod/calculo-do-frete-pelos-correios.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/732590-pbig/calculo-do-frete-pelos-correios.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22453]]></id><name><![CDATA[fastbay1]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[FastBay - eBay Marketplace synchronization]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Revenda (marketplace)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[FASTBAY&nbsp;is the professional solution to&nbsp;synchronize your Prestashop store towards your Ebay account in few minutes&nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[Prestalia]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/revenda-/22453-fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22453.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[FASTBAY&nbsp;is the professional solution to&nbsp;synchronize your Prestashop store towards your Ebay account in few minutes&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Over&nbsp;1,250,000 Ebay Listings&nbsp;have been&nbsp;already created with FastBay.EASY - A simplified configuration wizard will allow you to customize all settings without any problem in order to synchronize and manage products and orders.RELIABLE - Our module will assist you in every step of sync process and if you need assistance we guarantee a response&nbsp;within 48 hours.FLEXIBLE - FastBay guarantees many features that allows you to make a&nbsp;flexible site management&nbsp;that will suits all your needs.FAST - With our FastBay module your &#39;waiting times&#39; will be reduced beyond belief !&nbsp;Sync in a couple of minutes more than 5.000 products!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.5.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[299.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[219.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/748180-pprod/fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/748180-pbig/fastbay-ebay-marketplace-synchronization.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22666]]></id><name><![CDATA[onlinechat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Chat Online]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Suporte & Chat on-line]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo Online Chat desenvolvido pela PrestaShop, ofere&ccedil;a o chat on-line na sua loja e converse com os clientes]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/suporte-chat-on-line/22666-chat-online.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22666.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo Online Chat desenvolvido pela PrestaShop, ofere&ccedil;a o chat on-line na sua loja e converse com os clientes. Essa ferramenta de comunica&ccedil;&atilde;o, que se tornou imprescind&iacute;vel no e-commerce, permite orientar e aconselhar a clientela em tempo real, criando la&ccedil;os mais fortes.   Melhore sua rela&ccedil;&atilde;o com os clientes e seu servi&ccedil;o de p&oacute;s-venda com esse m&oacute;dulo que, al&eacute;m de n&atilde;o requerer assinatura, aumenta at&eacute; 40% da sua taxa de convers&atilde;o!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Sem necessidade de assinatura, em apenas alguns cliques &eacute; poss&iacute;vel configurar o m&oacute;dulo e iniciar conversas on-line com seus clientes!;&nbsp;A interface &eacute; simples, de uso f&aacute;cil, e o design perfeitamente adaptado ao seu site tanto no quesito da administra&ccedil;&atilde;o quanto da loja;&nbsp;Gra&ccedil;as a esses di&aacute;logos virtuais, voc&ecirc; estabelece uma rela&ccedil;&atilde;o mais humana e s&oacute;lida com os clientes, que se mant&ecirc;m fi&eacute;is &agrave; sua marca;&nbsp;Ao responder diretamente &agrave;s perguntas dos visitantes, a quantidade de carrinhos abandonados &eacute; diminu&iacute;da;&nbsp;Voc&ecirc; poupa tempo na gest&atilde;o do servi&ccedil;o de p&oacute;s-venda, resolvendo os problemas e cuidando dos pedidos em tempo real.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/752296-pprod/chat-online.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/752296-pbig/chat-online.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22779]]></id><name><![CDATA[sizeconversion]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Guia de Tamanho]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Tamanhos e dimensões]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Reduza as devolu&ccedil;&otilde;es de produto e satisfa&ccedil;a plenamente os clientes com o m&oacute;dulo&nbsp;Guia de Tamanho!   Ideal para&nbsp;lojas virtuais de roupas, lingerie, acess&oacute;rio]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/tamanhos-dimensoes/22779-guia-de-tamanho.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22779.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Reduza as devolu&ccedil;&otilde;es de produto e satisfa&ccedil;a plenamente os clientes com o m&oacute;dulo&nbsp;Guia de Tamanho!   Ideal para&nbsp;lojas virtuais de roupas, lingerie, acess&oacute;rios e joias, permite criar e personalizar, em apenas alguns minutos, tabelas de correspond&ecirc;ncia de tamanhos para os produtos e categorias de sua escolha.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Com esse m&oacute;dulo, crie guias de tamanho, que s&atilde;o ferramentas essenciais para:Ajudar clientes em d&uacute;vida a finalizarem a compra escolhendo o tamanho certo para elesReduzir as devolu&ccedil;&otilde;es&nbsp;e trocas devido a um erro de tamanhoEvitar carrinhos abandonados e aumentar a taxa de convers&atilde;o da sua loja]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/755429-pprod/guia-de-tamanho.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/755429-pbig/guia-de-tamanho.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23517]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_easyplaces]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Places]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cadastro e Processo de Pedido]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/cadastro-e-processo-de-pedido/23517-easy-places.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23517.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature. Help your customers save time and reduce the number of customers who give up whilst creating an account from now on!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our Easy Places module helps you increase your transformation rate by simplifying the order creation process, by providing a feature that automatically enters the account creation or order addresses.  - "OK, but why do I need that ?" - When a new customer wants to place an order on your shop, you have to ask them for their delivery and invoicing address. Your customers find this compulsory and repetitive step annoying and frustrating. Some customers give up and go to another site where they know they have already entered all their information. What is more, shipping errors caused by customers entering their addresses incorrectly are not uncommon, entailing additional transport costs and decreased customer satisfaction owing to the delays caused by their parcels being sent out and returned again.  Easy Places is the ultimate solution for avoiding such problems! It allows you to offer your clients an elegant, high performance technical solution to make your account creation forms more pleasant to fill in.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766068-pprod/easy-places.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/766068-pbig/easy-places.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23617]]></id><name><![CDATA[zendesk]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Official Zendesk]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SAC]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Contextualize your customer interactions by seeing their latest orders when managing tickets inside Zendesk]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/sac/23617-official-zendesk.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23617.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Contextualize your customer interactions by seeing their latest orders when managing tickets inside Zendesk. Order details such as status, total, creation date, and products names and quantities are all visible from within Zendesk. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[&nbsp;This integration will save customer support agents time and contextualize interactions as they no longer need to switch between Prestashop and Zendesk&#39;s interfaces to link a ticket to customer orders.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[23671]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookproductad]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Ads + Pixel for THE Social Network]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Remarketing & Compras abandonados]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Take advantage of Facebook’s unmatched targeting and ROI with Facebook product ads and remarketing]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/remarketing-compras-abandonados/23671-product-ads-pixel-for-the-social-network.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23671.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Take advantage of Facebook’s unmatched targeting and ROI with Facebook product ads and remarketing.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and customer repeat purchases on loyalty : Advertise your products on Facebook with Facebook Product Ads by exporting your product catalog to Facebook !  *** WINNER OF THE 2017 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  This is essentially the Facebook equivalent of Google Shopping / Merchant Center. But with unprecedented targeting options that Google can only dream of: age, sex, family situation, exact geographical location, interests, groups, pages and products liked, and all the impressive data Facebook has on each and everyone of your customers and prospects. An online marketer’s dream come true ! And the cost is also typically lower than Google’s, giving you a much better Return On Investment.  Just Like Google, Facebook has also implemented a Custom Audiences and Remarketing platform, allowing you to display ads to people who have previously visited your online shop or blog, and segmenting them in any way you see fit. Or you can also acquire new customers that are similar to your existing customers based on the information Facebook has on them and comparing it with information they have on your existing customers.  This is all done via the Facebook Pixel code, which also serves to track orders / conversions on your PrestaShop online store.  When you mix the Facebook Product Catalog with the Facebook Pixel, you get Dynamic Product Ads: the ability to retarget visitors from your site with the exact products they have viewed or with complementary ones. Dynamic Remarketing is extremely effective and offers a very high conversion rate and ROI.  This all-in-one module provides everything you need to get started right now with the world’s newest, most advanced and effective online advertising technology on the market. So, get on board TODAY so you don’t miss the boat !  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when we contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[129.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[159.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[114.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/835119-pprod/product-ads-pixel-for-the-social-network.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/835119-pbig/product-ads-pixel-for-the-social-network.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23805]]></id><name><![CDATA[dashturnoverbycategory]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Painel de Controle por Categoria]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Painéis de controle]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Impulsione o desempenho da sua loja acessando com facilidade as estat&iacute;sticas sobre as categorias do seu cat&aacute;logo de produto]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/paineis-de-controle/23805-painel-de-controle-por-categoria.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23805.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Impulsione o desempenho da sua loja acessando com facilidade as estat&iacute;sticas sobre as categorias do seu cat&aacute;logo de produto.&nbsp;Analise a atividade do seu site de e-commerce&nbsp;diretamente do painel de controle da loja e aprenda a otimizar as vendas.   Ajuste suas promo&ccedil;&otilde;es e estoques de produtos&nbsp;conforme os resultados!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Aumente suas convers&otilde;es&nbsp;aprofundando o conhecimento sobre o desempenho da sua loja.   Ganhe tempo&nbsp;visualizando as estat&iacute;sticas mais importantes do seu cat&aacute;logo em uma &uacute;nica tabela. Nada &eacute; mais f&aacute;cil do que isso, tudo pode ser feito do painel de controle do seu back-office!   Seja proativo&nbsp;para adaptar produtos, categorias, pre&ccedil;os e estoques, e operar novas campanhas promocionais para as categorias de produtos priorit&aacute;rias.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/772289-pprod/painel-de-controle-por-categoria.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/772289-pbig/painel-de-controle-por-categoria.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_subscription]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Subscription with automatic recurring payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Assinaturas (Box)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A new economic model was created few months ago within the world of e-commerce: subscription-based e-commerce]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/assinaturas-box/24345-advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A new economic model was created few months ago within the world of e-commerce: subscription-based e-commerce. Known mainly in box form, it is reaching and increasing number of sectors: ready-to-wear clothes, cosmetics, food products...]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Are you ready for subscription-based e-commerce?This is a business model that combines e-commerce and subscription retail. So what is the concept really all about?&nbsp;Subscription-based e-commerce is an excellent way for brands and retailers to begin a process of getting to know their client&egrave;le and establish customer loyalty: the real strength of this economic system is simply its powerful ability to generate customer loyalty!&nbsp;Another advantage is that subscription-based e-commerce enables you to benefit from recurring monthly revenue without having to rely on the acquisition of new customers. What&#39;s more, subscription-based e-commerce encourages consumers to indulge and to re-purchase your products if they are impressed.It stands to reason that there is no-one more loyal than a customer who pays a subscription, but be careful, there are a few down sides to the subscription nowadays: customers are developing an increasing dislike to being tied in. As a result you have to grant him a great deal of freedom; he must be able to cancel his subscription whenever he sees fit!&nbsp;If at the beginning of the month your customer no longer wishes to receive the product or products for which he has subscribed, it should not have to be delivered nor billed for. Nevertheless, the likelihood that the customer will continue to use the service is much more important than is the case with &quot;traditional&quot; e-commerce! It is the assurance of regular monthly turnover, alongside the ability to manage your stock levels.&nbsp;Our Advanced Subscription module for PrestaShop takes into account all of these precepts and saves you the precious time that would be required to implement them manually.&nbsp;The reason that the paid subscription model is developing so quickly within the area of e-commerce is that retail sites appear to find in it an effective solution by which to counteract one of the main issues that chips away at their profitability: delivery fees&nbsp;Amazon Premium, Fnac Express+, Cdiscount &agrave; volont&eacute;... Many e-commerce retailers are now launching their own paid subscription services. In order to grasp the reason behind the phenomenon, one need only remember the fact that delivery fees remain the leading cause of abandoned shopping carts and that, on average, a subscribing customer is twice as lucrative as a non-subscribing customer.&nbsp;A few figures to quantify the impact of delivery on e-business:&nbsp;87% of online shoppers systematically search for a means by which to avoid having to pay shipping fees (searching for a promotional code, addition of a product to the cart...).44% abandon their purchases purely and simply on account of these fees66% switch to a different retail site in search of delivery conditions that are acceptable to them.&nbsp;Converting customers into subscribers enables online retailers to save time and money compared to traditional methods of recovering customers and generating customer loyalty, as it allows you automate part of the customer relationship. This saving can then be allocated to a free delivery service reserved solely for your subscribers, thus eliminating this purchasing deterrent and in turn achieving much greater conversion rates.&nbsp;&nbsp;Objective: to generate long-term customer loyalty&nbsp;In addition to the appeal of novelty, subscription-based e-commerce represents a formidable double-edged sword for brands that are reliant on distribution networks and that are targeting growth. In actual fact, first and foremost the subscription principle allows retailers to generate recurrent turnover and a stable operating account.&nbsp;Thus, while subscription-based e-commerce may have cut its teeth with samples and travel-sized products, various other products now also appear to lend themselves to the model: in ready-to-wear clothing, cosmetics, culture and leisure, but also products intended for regular consumption such as mineral water or hygiene products (baby nappies for instance).&nbsp;&nbsp;Optimization of supply and of your logisticsThe subscription enables you to achieve an improved rate of re-purchase, thus allowing you to purchase from your suppliers more efficiently. In fact, our module will enable you to accurately predict which products will sell, in which quantity and at which frequency.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[499.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[599.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[439.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Loyalty"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-loyalty.png]]></badge><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/783025-pprod/advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/783025-pbig/advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24399]]></id><name><![CDATA[dashbypayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Painel de Controle – Formas de Pagamento]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Painéis de controle]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Impulsione o desempenho da sua loja adotando formas de pagamento rent&aacute;veis e perfeitamente adaptadas &agrave;s necessidades dos clientes!  Uma das suas formas de pagamento n&atilde;o est&aacute]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/paineis-de-controle/24399-painel-de-controle-formas-de-pagamento.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24399.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Impulsione o desempenho da sua loja adotando formas de pagamento rent&aacute;veis e perfeitamente adaptadas &agrave;s necessidades dos clientes!  Uma das suas formas de pagamento n&atilde;o est&aacute; funcionado bem? Agora voc&ecirc; n&atilde;o leva mais dias at&eacute; perceber!&nbsp;  Acesse as&nbsp;estat&iacute;sticas sobre as formas de pagamento da sua loja diretamente pelo painel de controle.&nbsp;Analise facilmente os neg&oacute;cios do seu site&nbsp;de acordo com as diversas formas de pagamento e aprenda a otimizar suas vendas.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Aumente suas convers&otilde;es&nbsp;aprofundando o conhecimento sobre o desempenho das suas formas de pagamento.   Ganhe tempo&nbsp;visualizando as estat&iacute;sticas mais importantes das formas de pagamento em uma &uacute;nica tabela. Nada &eacute; mais f&aacute;cil do que isso, tudo pode ser feito do painel de controle do seu back-office!   Seja proativo&nbsp;para selecionar as formas de pagamento que mais correspondem &agrave; sua clientela-alvo e destaque-as na p&aacute;gina inicial da loja, tranquilizando os clientes, e no funil de compra.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/784999-pprod/painel-de-controle-formas-de-pagamento.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/784999-pbig/painel-de-controle-formas-de-pagamento.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24894]]></id><name><![CDATA[autogoogleplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Address Autocomplete]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Cadastro e Processo de Pedido]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module makes it possible to fill, quickly and without any errors, the address field when yours clients are ordering]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/cadastro-e-processo-de-pedido/24894-google-address-autocomplete.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24894.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module makes it possible to fill, quickly and without any errors, the address field when yours clients are ordering. It automatically suggests the right address, and so improve yours customer&#39;s browsing comfort.&nbsp;An easy way to save time !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module uses Google Map&#39;s API for automatically fill your clients adresses when they register.Increase your turnover, reducing errors and delivery problems.Decrease product returns&#39; number.Improve your user&#39;s experience.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Criador parceiro de módulos"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/798639-pprod/google-address-autocomplete.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/798639-pbig/google-address-autocomplete.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24996]]></id><name><![CDATA[stripe_official]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Stripe official]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pagamento por cartão ou por carteira]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and charge payments securely with Stripe, the easiest way to accept online payments]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/pagamento-carta-carteira/24996-stripe-official.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24996.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase your conversion rate and charge payments securely with Stripe, the easiest way to accept online payments.​Install Stripe's plugin on your PrestaShop online store, create a Stripe account, and start accepting payments immediately. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Create your Stripe account in 10 minutes and immediately start accepting payments via Visa, MasterCard, American Express, SOFORT, Giropay, Bancontact and iDEAL (no additional contract/merchant ID needed from your bank)Improve your conversion rate by offering a seamless payment experience to your customers: Stripe lets you host the payment form on your own pages, without redirection to a bank third-part pageKeep your fraud under control thanks to customizable 3D-Secure and Stripe Radar, our suite of anti-fraud toolsHundreds of third-part integrations to enrich your Stripe set-up (invoicing, SMS...)&nbsp;This plugin fully relies on Stripe.js to&nbsp;generate&nbsp;a&nbsp;token&nbsp;that&nbsp;gets&nbsp;used&nbsp;to create the charge with Stripe: sensitive data will never hit your servers, maintaining a high level of security and preventing you from a heavy PCI/DSS certification.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[179.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/842278-pprod/stripe-official.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/842278-pbig/stripe-official.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26203]]></id><name><![CDATA[faviconotification]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Notificação na Aba do Navegador (Favicon)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[E-mails & Notícias]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Reduza o n&uacute;mero de carrinhos abandonados acrescentando uma notifica&ccedil;&atilde;o diretamente no navegador do cliente]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/emails-noticias/26203-notificacao-na-aba-do-navegador-favicon.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26203.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Reduza o n&uacute;mero de carrinhos abandonados acrescentando uma notifica&ccedil;&atilde;o diretamente no navegador do cliente.   Esse m&oacute;dulo pode ser instalado e configurado em apenas 30 segundos e indica, pr&oacute;ximo ao favicon da sua loja, a quantidade de produtos no carrinho de um cliente. &Eacute; um empurr&atilde;ozinho discreto e eficaz para que os usu&aacute;rios n&atilde;o esque&ccedil;am os produtos do carrinho e finalizem a compra!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[O m&oacute;dulo Notifica&ccedil;&atilde;o na Aba do Navegador permite:Reduzir os itens abandonados&nbsp;por meio de uma notifica&ccedil;&atilde;o &agrave; direita no navegador;Aumentar facilmente a taxa de convers&atilde;o da sua loja: o m&oacute;dulo &eacute; ativado com apenas um clique, sem nenhum impacto no tema, design ou navega&ccedil;&atilde;o!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/824350-pprod/notificacao-na-aba-do-navegador-favicon.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/824350-pbig/notificacao-na-aba-do-navegador-favicon.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26233]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestashop 1.7 user guide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop 1.7 User Guide (English version)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Guia do usuário]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Mais de 300 p&aacute;ginas e dicas em ingl&ecirc;s para gui&aacute;-lo passo a passo! Com o Guia do Usu&aacute;rio Oficial PrestaShop 1]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/guia-do-usuario/26233-prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26233.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Mais de 300 p&aacute;ginas e dicas em ingl&ecirc;s para gui&aacute;-lo passo a passo! Com o Guia do Usu&aacute;rio Oficial PrestaShop 1.7 (em ingl&ecirc;s) em formato PDF, saiba como configurar facilmente a sua loja e utilizar todo o seu potencial para aumentar o seu tr&aacute;fego, suas vendas e seu faturamento.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Aproveite ao m&aacute;ximo os recursos&nbsp;que a sua loja PrestaShop oferece!Ganhe tempo&nbsp;dominando perfeitamente a sua lojaCom este guia de usu&aacute;rio, voc&ecirc; conhecer&aacute; todos os recursos dispon&iacute;veis em sua loja PrestaShop 1.7. Logo voc&ecirc; poder&aacute; administrar facilmente sua loja PrestaShop, ganhar tempo na gest&atilde;o di&aacute;ria e otimizar suas vendas.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[14.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[16.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[13.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/824674-pprod/prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/824674-pbig/prestashop-17-user-guide-english-version.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26784]]></id><name><![CDATA[todolist]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[To Do List (in your back office)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Ferramentas de Administração]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Acesse suas tarefas diretamente a partir do painel de controle de sua loja!   Agora voc&ecirc; n&atilde;o precisa mais usar diversos softwares: o m&oacute;dulo Lista de Afazeres est&aacute; inclu&iacu]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/ferramentas-administracao/26784-to-do-list-in-your-back-office.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26784.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Acesse suas tarefas diretamente a partir do painel de controle de sua loja!   Agora voc&ecirc; n&atilde;o precisa mais usar diversos softwares: o m&oacute;dulo Lista de Afazeres est&aacute; inclu&iacute;do em seu back-office e lhe permite criar, editar, priorizar e classificar todas as suas tarefas para economizar tempo todos os dias!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[O m&oacute;dulo Lista de Afazeres da PrestaShop permite:Visualizar todas as a&ccedil;&otilde;es a serem tomadas em sua loja diretamente a partir do seu painel de controle, sem precisar utilizar um outro aplicativoPriorizar suas tarefas em fun&ccedil;&atilde;o do grau de urg&ecirc;ncia de cada a&ccedil;&atilde;o a ser realizadaGanhar tempo e produtividade permitindo classificar as tarefas (pedidos em andamento, estoques a renovar, promo&ccedil;&atilde;o a ser elaborada...),Criar tarefas em um &uacute;nico clique&nbsp;Acessar tudo que foi realizado visualizando as tarefas conclu&iacute;das em uma outra abaAtribuir a realiza&ccedil;&atilde;o de uma tarefa &agrave; pessoa que voc&ecirc; desejar que tenha uma Conta de Funcion&aacute;rio no back-office de sua loja.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[39.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/838558-pprod/to-do-list-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/838558-pbig/to-do-list-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26835]]></id><name><![CDATA[buylater]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Buy Later]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Lista de desejos & Vale-presente]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Um dos principais recursos dos grandes sites de e-commerce, acrescentar o &quot;Buy Later&rdquo; (salvar o produto para comprar mais tarde)&nbsp;no resumo do carrinho de compra &eacute; indispens&aacu]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/lista-desejos-vale-presente/26835-buy-later.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26835.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Um dos principais recursos dos grandes sites de e-commerce, acrescentar o &quot;Buy Later&rdquo; (salvar o produto para comprar mais tarde)&nbsp;no resumo do carrinho de compra &eacute; indispens&aacute;vel para aumentar suas vendas e taxa de convers&atilde;o.&nbsp; &nbsp; Com apenas um clique (muito mais r&aacute;pido do que uma lista de desejos), seus clientes podem colocar de lado os produtos selecionados e passar o pedido posteriormente.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Aprimore a experi&ecirc;ncia do usu&aacute;rio&nbsp;oferecendo um recurso caro aos clientes dos maiores sites de e-commerce (Amazon, etc.) no resumo do carrinho;&nbsp;Aumente o carrinho m&eacute;dio dos clientes: eles esqueceram os produtos separados durante uma visita anterior, mas dessa vez ir&atilde;o coloc&aacute;-los no carrinho mesmo sem essa inten&ccedil;&atilde;o inicialmente;&nbsp;Melhore o resumo do carrinho de compra permitindo que os clientes listem seus produtos preferidos e os coloquem de lado;&nbsp;Impulsione suas vendas&nbsp;permitindo que encontrem esses itens em uma pr&oacute;xima visita e os coloquem novamente no carrinho;&nbsp;Retenha seus clientes&nbsp;permitindo que separem um produto que gostaram para a pr&oacute;xima compra;&nbsp;Estimule compras impulsivas&nbsp;indicando quando esses produtos estiverem em promo&ccedil;&atilde;o ou o estoque estiver baixo.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.7]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/839317-pprod/buy-later.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/839317-pbig/buy-later.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26876]]></id><name><![CDATA[topbanner]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Top Banner]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Blocos, Guias & Banners]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo Top Banner,&nbsp;aumente o impacto das suas vendas, ofertas especiais e seu faturamento]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/blocos-guias-banners/26876-top-banner.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26876.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo Top Banner,&nbsp;aumente o impacto das suas vendas, ofertas especiais e seu faturamento.&nbsp;Exiba um&nbsp;banner para incentivar a compra com uma contagem regressiva em todas as p&aacute;ginas do seu site! &nbsp; Comunique de modo f&aacute;cil e eficaz com todos os visitantes durante o percurso de compra por meio de uma exibi&ccedil;&atilde;o personalizada e mensagens nos banners.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Destaque seus c&oacute;digos promocionais e obtenha promo&ccedil;&otilde;es, sald&otilde;es e vendas-rel&acirc;mpago bem-sucedidosAproximadamente 60% dos internautas abandonam a compra se n&atilde;o encontrarem um c&oacute;digo promocional (estudo do Mailorama). Gra&ccedil;as aos banners, seus clientes n&atilde;o perder&atilde;o nenhuma oportunidade de comprar, aprimorando a experi&ecirc;ncia geral.Comunique com todos os visitantes de modo f&aacute;cil e eficazAo lan&ccedil;ar uma nova cole&ccedil;&atilde;o, anunciar uma oferta especial ou em datas imperd&iacute;veis (Natal, Black Friday, etc.), o banner &eacute; o meio ideal para comunicar com os internautas.  &nbsp;Impulsione suas convers&otilde;es e faturamentoAs mensagens e elementos de incentivo (c&oacute;digo promocional, cron&ocirc;metro, etc.) contidos no banner, constantemente exibido no seu site, encorajam os clientes a finalizar a compra antes que a oferta promocional termine.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/896453-pprod/top-banner.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/896453-pbig/top-banner.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26877]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoimg]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Image]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[SEO (Referenciamento natural)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Apesar de as descri&ccedil;&otilde;es das imagens serem um recurso de SEO pouco aplicado nas p&aacute;ginas de produto, uma descri&ccedil;&atilde;o espec&iacute;fica&nbsp;&eacute; um meio infal&iacute]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/seo-referenciamento-natural/26877-seo-image.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26877.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Apesar de as descri&ccedil;&otilde;es das imagens serem um recurso de SEO pouco aplicado nas p&aacute;ginas de produto, uma descri&ccedil;&atilde;o espec&iacute;fica&nbsp;&eacute; um meio infal&iacute;vel de aumentar a visibilidade da sua loja virtual nos mecanismos de busca. &nbsp;  O m&oacute;dulo SEO&nbsp;Images (Tag Alt)&nbsp;automatiza a cria&ccedil;&atilde;o de tags Alt para imagens de produtos e fornece conte&uacute;do de qualidade com o intuito de melhorar a posi&ccedil;&atilde;o da p&aacute;gina do seu site.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Ganhe tempo com o SEO e aproveite as vantagens do SEO das suas imagens com a escrita autom&aacute;tica das tags Alt! &nbsp; Por meio do m&oacute;dulo SEO Images (Tag Alt):Suba sua posi&ccedil;&atilde;o nos mecanismos de buscaAumente as vendas exponencialmente com uma melhor visibilidade das suas p&aacute;ginas de produtoAumente as taxas de convers&atilde;o com tr&aacute;fego ultraqualificadoDestaque-se da concorr&ecirc;ncia com regras diferenciadas para o SEO das suas imagens]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[74.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/840258-pprod/seo-image.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/840258-pbig/seo-image.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27274]]></id><name><![CDATA[pscookiebanner]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cookie Banner + CMS]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Jurídico]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The Cookie Policy Banner + CMS developed by PrestaShop helps you meet the EU Cookie law requirements by displaying on your online store a customizable and configurable warning banner in just a few cli]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/juridico/27274-cookie-banner-cms.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27274.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The Cookie Policy Banner + CMS developed by PrestaShop helps you meet the EU Cookie law requirements by displaying on your online store a customizable and configurable warning banner in just a few clicks. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows you to be fully in compliance with the European policy of cookies management, informing your customers and prospects of the cookies and other tracers installed on your website&nbsp;It displays a warning banner at the arrival of the visitors on your shop, entirely responsive and customizable, from the formatting of the banner to the displayed text to guarantee a perfect adaptation to your shop.&nbsp;You are accompanied in the creation and redaction of your cookie policy page containing the main information on the use of cookies on your website. A document with useful links is provided to help you write the content of this page.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/873820-pprod/cookie-banner-cms.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/873820-pbig/cookie-banner-cms.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27535]]></id><name><![CDATA[psproductstats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Essential Product Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Análises & Estatísticas]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Em um piscar de olhos e de cada ficha de produto, tenha acesso a todas as estat&iacute;sticas mais importantes para aumentar o desempenho de cada produto e impulsionar suas vendas!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/analises-estatisticas/27535-essential-product-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Em um piscar de olhos e de cada ficha de produto, tenha acesso a todas as estat&iacute;sticas mais importantes para aumentar o desempenho de cada produto e impulsionar suas vendas!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Com o m&oacute;dulo Estat&iacute;sticas de Produtos, desenvolvido pela PrestaShop, encontre para cada item e no per&iacute;odo desejado: &nbsp; As informa&ccedil;&otilde;es sobre as vendas e a renda gerada:A curva das vendas realizadas;O faturamento bruto;O faturamento l&iacute;quido;O perfil dos consumidores por:Sexo;Idade;Pa&iacute;s;Prefer&ecirc;ncias de pagamento;Prefer&ecirc;ncias de entrega.&nbsp; A compara&ccedil;&atilde;o do desempenho desse produto com os outros itens da mesma categoria no per&iacute;odo selecionado, em termos de:Quantidade de vendas;Faturamento;Taxa de convers&atilde;o;Abandono de carrinhos;Taxa de reembolso.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/880939-pprod/essential-product-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/880939-pbig/essential-product-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27562]]></id><name><![CDATA[pshomeslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Controle deslizante da página inicial]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Sliders & Galerias]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Gra&ccedil;as ao m&oacute;dulo Homepage Slider, comunique-se com efici&ecirc;ncia com os seus visitantes exibindo um slider de tela cheia e responsivo em sua p&aacute;gina inicial! &nbsp; Com este sli]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/sliders-galerias/27562-controle-deslizante-da-pagina-inicial.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27562.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Gra&ccedil;as ao m&oacute;dulo Homepage Slider, comunique-se com efici&ecirc;ncia com os seus visitantes exibindo um slider de tela cheia e responsivo em sua p&aacute;gina inicial! &nbsp; Com este slider personaliz&aacute;vel em alguns minutos, modernize a exibi&ccedil;&atilde;o de sua p&aacute;gina inicial e atraia imediatamente a aten&ccedil;&atilde;o de seus visitantes desde sua chegada &agrave; loja!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Modernize e enrique&ccedil;a sua p&aacute;gina inicial mantendo um design simples apresentando todo o seu conte&uacute;do importante em um controle deslizante no formato e estilo que voc&ecirc; escolher.&nbsp;Destaque suas informa&ccedil;&otilde;es desejadas e tenha sucesso em suas campanhas de comunica&ccedil;&atilde;oQuer voc&ecirc; esteja lan&ccedil;ando novos produtos, promovendo ou anunciando eventos futuros, o controle deslizante permite garantir a m&aacute;xima visibilidade da sua mensagem na p&aacute;gina inicial da sua loja e incentivar os visitantes a conhecer seu conte&uacute;do.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[49.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/884765-pprod/controle-deslizante-da-pagina-inicial.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/884765-pbig/controle-deslizante-da-pagina-inicial.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27869]]></id><name><![CDATA[mtarget]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[MTarget SMS]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Boletim informativo & SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Use the power of the SMS to reassure your clients and increase your sales!Sales status, shopping basket reminder, birthdays or Marketing Cible campaigns, give your shop an extra breath with our SMS mo]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/pt/boletim-informativo-sms/27869-mtarget-sms.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-PT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27869.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Use the power of the SMS to reassure your clients and increase your sales!Sales status, shopping basket reminder, birthdays or Marketing Cible campaigns, give your shop an extra breath with our SMS module.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Strengthen your client relations and increase your sales thanks to our handy and simple SMS sending solution.&nbsp;Inform your clients in real time of the progression of their purchaseRemind them of their current shopping basketCommunicate efficiently on all your events (sales, private sales, &hellip;)Segment and synchronize automatically your contacts on our platformBe informed by SMS about any new subscriptions, new orders and purchases or return demandsFollow and analyse the results of your campaignsManage your budget (no subscription, no hidden costs)After sale services and support based in FranceLowest price on&nbsp; the market]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.2.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/890985-pprod/mtarget-sms.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/890985-pbig/mtarget-sms.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>